-==http://www.1000fr.net==-
謦`L影su出品
本字幕H供W交流 澜用於商I用途
y以置信 打了一子球 s依然λ知之甚微
――米奇.曼陀(棒球巨星)
尼.戴蒙打 一那 我正在D播
Ball one to Johnny Damon and we are under way.
戴蒙的18打抵杏8支安打
Damon has eight hits in 18 at bats,
一支二景泊 一支三景泊 纱伪I
a double, a triple, a couple of stolen bases.
他在季首霰荣中舫4支安打
He had four hits in the series opener.
好球
Strike.
2001年 10月15日
球舻接彝庖斑 戴蒙@支是界惹
Down the right-field line, fair off the bat of Damon.
斯e塞漏接
It rolls by Spencer.
第一棒的戴蒙用一支 安打站上了二
And Damon will coast into second base with a leadoff double.
美盟季後 分^淘汰
球w入中右外野 喟 落下砹 是安打
Into right-center field, broken bat, it'll fall, a base hit.
他在示意戴蒙n回本 他要得分了
They waVe around Damon. He will score.
苌.吉安比在第一局
And Jason Giambi deliVers
舫鲆景泊蛩完友回镜梅
with a run-scoring single here in the opening inning.
W克m\蛹谊取得1比0I先
And the Athletics haVe taken that 1-nothing lead.
加油啊 要保住
Go, come on, now. We gotta spin it.
114，457，768美元 VS 39，722，689美元
~s洋基 VS W克m\蛹
上啊 洋基
Let's go, Yankees!
M
Bases loaded.
洋基如果可以舫龆景泊 就有C追平 F在2比0落後
The Yankees haVe the tying run at second, down 2-nothing.
\蛹谊漏接 忙得M鲲w球
The A 's are kicking it and throwing it all oVer the field.
如果不so{整B 他⒈惶蕴
And it might lead to their elimination if they don't get it right in a hurry.
重羧敬蚪右外野 Z斯蒂斯
Hammered down the right-field line. Justice!
洋基I先了
The Yankees haVe taken the lead.
片名 魔球
他辛⒅ 期待又一次
They're standing, anticipating another trip
挺M盟冠的旅程
to the League championship Series.
洋基只需解Q最後一打者
The Yankees one out away.
埃Y克.伯恩斯 他在洋基主鲞]有打
Eric Byrnes, never with an at bat in Yankee Stadium,
@次估也不有什N孬@
and they don't get much bigger than this one.
孤注一S也未必有Y果
Or more hectic when you're up there trying to get a job done.
-=LFRM字幕M=- 翻g: 十三月 霹Z哼哼 校: 瞳
]棒落空
And they're a strike away.
布朗克斯M是g呼（洋基主鏊在地）
And they're roaring in the Bronx.
洋基在五黾踞岱^中(53伲 的前鲋鍪Ю
Losing the first two games at home in the best-of-fiVe series
and roar back to...
洋基⒑葱l自己的冠^
The Yankees will defend their title.
]PS  它_著吧
It's okay, Joe, you can leave it on.
- 我可以不看 -  _著
I don't need to watch. Joe, leave it on.
好吧
Okay.
想像一下 作檠蠡T
Imagine how bad it'd be if you were a Yankee player
s不喜g喝香怎Nk
and didn't like the taste of champagne.
只能求D吧
Better ask to get traded.
必o洋基…
You gotta giVe the Yankees...
…A得冠
- win the big game.
接下⑹窃拥谋荣…
What a series that is gonna be in the next...
你知道有多少孩子穿著吉安比
You know how many kids are wearing Giambi's...?
吉安比在W克m的\犹咨 帽子 像和海
You know, Oakland Giambi's jerseys and hats and pictures and posters?
- 洋基七月磉@Yr@些孩子u一片 - 希望如此
Those same kids will be booing in July when the Yankees come here.
到底是吉安比落井下石 是|岸的~臭商人^分
Is it Giambi that's stabbing the back or the Pinstripes on the East coast?
你不能怪他巧取豪Z
You can't blame them for pilfering the henhouse.
- Y源[著不能浪M啊 - 什N叫不能怪他
The henhouse is there. I can't blame them?
六年Y他出了1|2千f美元
They're offering $ 120 million oVer six years.
~s洋基比我X多 他意o他出大rX
The Yankees haVe deeper pockets and they're willing to giVe him money.
他在收割我的T
They're pilfering our players.
好像我是~s洋基的菜地似的
It's like we're a farm system for the new York Yankees.
- T打得怎N - 他很害
How are the guys doing? That was a killer.
很害 很y啃下 @…
That was a killer. It's a tough one to swallow. It's...
- 他打得很好 - 就差^B嵫了
They played great. They played their hearts out.
他M力了 打得很精彩 只是Y果不M如人意
They did. They played fantastic. It just didn't fall our way.
- 明年你打得更好 - 不^就差一c啊 是吧
You'll do better next year. But we were close, though.
很接近了 就差一c
We were so close. Right there.
差c就倮了 你_心的
Almost had it. You gotta feel good about that.
我_心死了 _心O了
I feel great about it. I feel great about it.
唔
Um...
明年不打得更好
We're not gonna do better next year.
- 槭颤N - 你知道我正被人~肉
Why not? Well, you know we're being gutted.
吉安比 戴蒙和伊斯林豪森都要走了
We're losing Giambi, Damon, Isringhausen.
都定了 我麻┖艽
Done deal. We're in trouble.
你能找到新人的 初就是你lF了苌和戴蒙
You'll find new guys. You found Jason, you found Damon.
- 我要更多的Y金 史蒂夫 - 比利
I need more money, Steve. Billy.
- 我需要X - 我]X了
I need more money. We don't have any.
我不能用3800f美元去抗衡1|2千f啊
I can't compete against $ 120 million with $38 million.
我不能和有更大A算的伍比
We're not gonna compete with these teams that have big budgets.
我必在自己能力冗\作
We're gonna work within the constraints we have,
而你要M全力招募新T
and you're gonna do the best job that you can recruiting new players.
我]法每年付oT1700f
We're not gonna pay $ 17 million to players.
我又]要你出…
I'm not asking you
1千f 2千f或3千f
for 10 or 20, 30 million dollars.
我只要求一c椭
I'm just asking for a bit of help.
再臀乙幌 我就能湍憬M成冠
Get me a little closer and I will get you that championship team.
你雇我就是榱诉@ @就是我的工作
I mean, this is why I'm here. This is why you hired me.
我要 我在@嘿M什N…
And I gotta ask you, what are we doing here
- 比利 我... - …如果不是想A冠
Billy, l... if it's not to win a championship?
- 我也很想… - 我的目司驮谶@Y @Y
I wanna win just as much... That's my bar. My bar is here.
目耸шA得冠
My bar is to take this team to the championship.
比利 我是小市銮蜿 你是小市銮蜿的理
Billy, we're a small-market team, and you're a small-market GM.
我不能付出我]有的X 你面ΜF
I'm asking you to be okay not spending money that I don't have.
你深呼吸一口
And I'm asking you to take a deep breath,
忘掉失 回到Y去
shake off the loss, get back in a room with your guys,
想k法用我手^的X
and figure out how to find replacements for the guys we lost
找到能替代x_T的新人
with the money that we do have.
我不走 我不能就@幼甙
I'm not leaving here. I'm not... I can't leave here with that.
我能湍闶颤N
What else can I help you with?
@_r太好了 你得想k法s超 我…
It's a good offer, and you gotta match it. L...
我需要一crg
I need another day.
他很Q 我想你明白
His mind's pretty made up. I just think you should know that.
- 有M 我一捍蚪o你 - 我一定D告他的
I got a call. I'll get you back. I'll let him know.
再
Bye.
- 喂 - 比利 是我 史考特
Yeah? Billy, Scott.
- 跟丹通了 - 不是吧
Just got off the phone with Dan. You didn't.
他打o我 我很@
I was surprised he called me.
住口 我o尼_r750f 他不e人效力
Stop. I got Johnny for 7.5 or he doesn't play anywhere else.
- @是你答的 - 波士D加a到775f
That's the deal you made. Boston just upped it to 7. 75.
你在
You there?
- 我f好的 史考特 - 是f好了 如果你能加到800f
We had a deal, Scott. We haVe a deal, if it's 8 million.
- 夥 你耍我啊 - 我只是榭舴
Oh, man, you played me. I'm just doing my job for my client.
不 你是耍我 而且你F在也在耍我
No, you're playing me, and you're still playing me.
恭喜你 混蛋 你A了
Congratulations, asshole. You win.
我喜g屁股上Lc毛的砘
I like guys that got a little hair on their ass.
坦白f 他是曼托或者梅斯那哟蔚
He looks like a Mantle or a Mays, quite frankly.
- 他天生就是棒球手的w魄 - R蒂 你找到l了
He's got a baseball body. Matty, who do you got?
- 我喜g吉拉尼莫 -
I like Geronimo. Yes.
@砘锸呛眠\T K^大 速度快 有天x
The guy's an athlete. Big, fast, talented.
- 我手Y排第一的 - L得好看 廓r明
Top of my list. Clean-cut, good face.
-  下巴很 - 全能型的
Yeah, good jaw. Five-tools guy.
- L得不e的球手 - 擅L打
Good-Iooking ballplayer. Can he hit?
- 他]棒姿莺芷亮 是吧 苋鹈 - 他能把球打爆
He's got a beautiful swing. The ball explodes off his bat.
他用棒尖羟 接|到球r
He throws the club head at the ball, and when he connects,
他用力舫 球砰地w走
he drives it, it pops off the bat.
- 整球龆寄苈到 - 糁新屎芨
You can hear it all over the ballpark. A lot of pop.
如果他很打 槭颤N打得不好
If he's good, why doesn't he hit good?
- 他是好打者 - t早他出^的
He is a good hitter. He'll be ready.
他好得足以抵抗大盟投手
He's gonna be a good hitter against big-league arms?
- 不e的 - 我不@N想
Could be great. I don't think so.
新人需要打 超^四百 他就好
Kid needs at bats. Give him 400 at bats, he's gonna get better.
他可以打的
He can play.
他可以指哪打哪
He's hit everywhere along the line.
他就是我要的人
He's one of our guys.
好 我^m
Okay, let's move on.
- 阿迪 你喜gl - 我喜g佩雷斯 他的羟蜃莺
Artie, who do you like? I like Perez. He's got a classic swing.
- ^κ峭昝来 - 我不X得 他能打曲球
It's a real clean stroke. I don't know. Can't hit the curveball.
需要改M 我承J 不^他也值得P注
There's some work to be done, I'll admit that, but he's noticeable.
- 女朋友很h - 什N意思
Got an ugly girlfriend. What's that mean?
- 女朋友丑C明他]自信 - 好吧
Ugly girlfriend means no confidence.
你都昏^了 阿迪是Φ @人很有架
You are full of it. Artie is right. This guy's got an attitude.
有架菔呛檬
An attitude is good.
他就是那N人]走M 已雄L高昂的人
He walks in a room, his dick's already been there for two minutes.
他K非是A而不的 恰恰外型是不e
He passes the eye-candy test. Got the looks.
他已浜昧 就是需要比
He's ready to play the part. He just needs playing time.
我只是f他的女朋友RR虎虎
I'm just saying, his girlfriend is a six at best.
- 如果要代替吉安比 他行 - 巴拉巴拉
Look, if we're trying to replace Giambi, this guy could be it.
- 我同意 - 巴拉巴拉巴拉
I agree with you. La-la-la-la-la.
鬼 比利 你是想提建h
Damn, Billy, was that a suggestion?
夥 你就f]完
Guys, you're just talking.
f啊f 啦啦啦啦 好像@是例行公事
Talking, "la-la-la-la-la," like this is business as usual.
但不是
It's not.
我在努力解Q} 比利
We're trying to solve the problem.
不是@拥 你都]正}
Not like this. You're not looking at the problem.
我很清楚}是什N 我是f…
We're very aware of the problem. I mean...
好吧 }是什N
Okay, good. What's the problem?
著 比利 我都知道}何在 我必找人代替…
Look, Billy, we all understand what the problem is. We have to...
很好 }是什N
Okay, good. What's the problem?
}是我要找人代替 三重要T
We have to replace three key players in our lineup.
不 }是什N
Nope. What's the problem?
山姆f了 我要a上空缺的…
We gotta replace these guys with what we have...
不 }是什N 瑞
No. What's the problem, Barry?
我需要找到38全敬 120打c 47二景泊
We need 38 home runs, 120 RBIs and 47 doubles to replace.
我要解Q的}是 如果@是有X球
The problem we're trying to solve is that there are rich teams
@Y是F 然後下面是f不清的垃圾
and there are poor teams, then there's 50 feet of crap,
然後才是我
and then there's us.
@是不公平的比
It's an unfair game.
F在我正被人宰割 就像在o富人捐I器官
And now we've been gutted. We're like organ donors for the rich.
波士D拿走了我的IK 洋基拿走了我的心K
Boston's taken our kidneys, Yankees have taken our heart.
而你坐在@Y
And you guys sit around
f什N"好w魄"的屁 好像我只是在u牛仔
talking the same old "good body" nonsense like we're selling jeans.
好像我在找法比W （身材一流的意大利籍男星）
Like we're looking for Fabio.
我必D思路
We got to think differently.
我是吊尾的
We are the last dog at the bowl.
你知道最弱的狗崽 什N下 I死
You see what happens to the runt of the litter? He dies.
比利 @故事很感人 真的
Billy, that's a very touching story and everything,
但我想我都很清楚F在的情r
but I think we're all very much aware of what we're facing.
你是我中g最有最有智慧的
You have a lot of experience and wisdom in this room.
你需要ξ有c信心 我找到能代替吉安比的人
You need to have a little faith and let us do the job of replacing Giambi.
有像吉安比@拥囊臼
Is there another first baseman like Giambi?
- ]有了 - ]有
No, not really. No.
- 如果有 我能I得起 - 不行
If there was, could we afford him? Nope.
那你屁
Then what the fuck are you talking about, man?
如果我在@像洋基那有惺
If we try to play like the Yankees in here,
在錾衔得一塌T地
we will lose to the Yankees out there.
@起硐窨辗旱拇笤而已 比利
Boy, that sounds like fortune-cookie wisdom to me, Billy.
- 不 @是思考 - l是法比W啊
No, that's just logic. Who's Fabio?
他是游羰 西雅D人
He's a shortstop. He's a shortstop from Seattle.
F在]rg恐慌了
Now, this is no time to push the panic button.
比利 我的球探物色球T 然後M行培
Our scouts will find players, Player Development will develop them.
我教他成 W克m\蛹谊的球手
We'll teach them to play Oakland A baseball.
- 各位… - ]有阂 但我一直@幼龅
With all due respect, we've been doing this a long time.
你把替代吉安比的事交o我
Why don't you just let us be responsible for replacing Giambi
我去找能偃蔚娜
with who we know that can play?
- 力道普通 - 垮
Easy power. And loose.
@O子可以M首l容
This son of a bitch is going in the first round.
你是秀的x手 比利
You're a premium player, Billy.
你能跑 能守 能投 能打
You can run, you can field, you can throw, you can hit,
可以大力羟
you can hit with power.
@K不多
That doesn't come along Very often.
- @是姆.R丁人 球探 - 很高dJR你
This is Tom Martinez, national cross-checker.
- 你好 - 比利.e恩
How you doing? Billy Beane.
很高dJR你
Nice to meet you.
已有段rg]看到全能型x手了
It's been a while since I've seen a five-tool guy that can do everything.
我期望你加入棒的d趣
I'm hopeful your interest in professional baseball
和我一夂 我可以一同前M
is as strong as ours is gonna be in getting you in this upcoming draft.
e恩先生
WOMr. Beane?
R克可以您了
Mark is ready to see you now.
- 你今天好 - 我很好
How you doing? WOI'm fine.
How are you? Good.
- 嘿 比利 - 嗨 R克
Hey, Billy. Hey, Mark.
到你真高d 坐
Good to see you. Please sit down. You too.
- @是我的夥 夥 @位是比利 - 大家好
These are the guys. Guys, Billy. Boys.
- 近r如何 - 不e 你怎
How's it going? All right. How you been?
- 你坐@椅子很像影 - 我已坐了三周了
You're filling out that chair nicely. I got three weeks in it right now.
很好 兄弟
Good, good, man.
- 嗯 你怎幽 - 很不e
Yeah, man. How you doing? Fantastic.
- 好O了 - 再好不^了
Awesome. Couldn't be better.
真是好消息 我不想浪M你的rg
That's good to hear. I'm not gonna waste your time.
你直接f你要什N吧
You just tell me what you're looking for.
加薪5000f
Fifty million dollars in additional payroll.
你找吉安比要
You should try Giambi.
- 正中痛 - 抱歉 _玩笑太早了 是吧
Ouch. I'm sorry. Too soon, right?
我想本次面友善一些
I want this to be a friendly meeting.
但@不全是你的任吧
It's not all on your shoulders.
- 史蒂夫怎Nf - 史蒂夫]}
Where's Steve in this? Steve's great.
他100%全力支持重建伍
He's supportive in rebuilding this team.
我正想@N做
That's what we're gonna do.
- 那你想要什N - 左投後援投手
So, what are you looking for? A left-handed reliever.
我想要Y卡多.林康
I'm thinking Ricardo Rincon.
不可能的
That's not gonna happen.
都不能
Not even a discussion?
比利 就算你I得起 e介意我@Nf 我也很喜g他
Billy, even if you could afford him, respectfully, we love him.
我不D的
We're not about to let him go.
但你I了北卡_R拉的 委热鹄新人 不是
You got this Venezuelan kid coming up.
]e 已Do底特律了
We had him. We moved him to Detroit.
- 哈 - 有什N想法
Huh. What else you thinking?
外野手
Outfielders.
- 代替戴蒙 -
To replace Damon? Yeah.
- 就你能出的r格? 我]有阂夤 - 足蛄 R克
In your price range? No disrespect. Enough, Mark.
呃...哈林斯?
Uh... Hollins?
不
Uh-uh.
- 加西? - 不行
Garcia? No.
那N 科斯特
Maybe Coste.
哼
Uh-uh.
只能@恿
That's it.
- 好吧 就加西吧 - 泶替尼.戴蒙
All right, tell me about Garcia. To replace Johnny Damon?
- R克 他健康]}吧 -  他正在恢
Mark, is he healthy? Yeah, he's healthy-ish.
不m你f 他背有c} 是吧
He had that back thing.
- 春季就能出了 - 我直f吧
He'll be ready for spring ball. I'll tell you what.
如果你NcX 我可以Q格思Y
I can give you Guthrie if you kick in some cash.
- R克.格思Y？ -
Mark Guthrie? Yeah.
- 多少X - 20f
How much cash? Two hundred K.
好
Okay.
- 不能o你加西 - 你逗我的吧
So Garcia's gonna be a no. You're kidding me, right?
- 你_玩笑 - ]有
You're kidding me. I'm not.
好吧 加西Q格思Y 不NX
Okay. Straight up, Garcia for Guthrie, no kicker.
- 不NX了? - 一清二楚
No kicker? Straight up.
加西^Σ恍 但我能e人
I think it's gonna be a hard no on Garcia, but let's just keep going.
- 你有想要的 - @是致锇 我是在做生意吧
What else you thinking? What are we doing? Is this business?
我在克利夫m就@N做生意
This is the way we do business in Cleveland.
嘿
Hey.
- 你好 - 你是l
Hello. Who are you?
我是皮特.布m德
I'm Peter Brand.
你做什N的
What do you do?
我是R克.史派_的特e助理
I'm special assistant to Mark Shapiro.
所以 你做什N的
So, what do you do?
F在基本上是球T分析u估
Mostly player analysis right now.
工作多久了 是在棒球界的第一份工作?
Been on the job long? First job in baseball?
@就是我的第一份工作
It's my first job anywhere.
- 哇 恭喜啊 - xx
Wow, congrats. Thank you.
第一份工作 你是l的侄子
First job. Whose nephew are you?
R克槭颤N你的
Why does Mark listen to you?
我不J椤
I don't think, uh...
我不J樗常我的
I don't think he does very often.
但才有
He just did.
在那N情r下
Well, in that circumstance,
我想他其是布斯的 不是我的
I think he was more listening to Bruce than myself.
嗯 你是l
Mm-hm. Who are you?
我是皮特.布m德
I'm Peter Brand.
我才他不管你叫什N
I don't give a rat's ass what your name is.
才是怎N回事
What happened in there?
才在Y面是怎N回事
What happened in that room?
我不太清楚你想什N e恩先生
I'm not quite sure what you're asking me, Mr. Beane.
你跟布斯f了什N
What did you tell Bruce?
- 我只是f我喜g加西 - 你槭颤N喜g加西
I just told Bruce I like Garcia. You like Garcia. Why?
槭颤N
Why?
我不知道
I don't know. Ahem.
在@圈子Y 有N蔓延性的
There is an epidemic failure within the game
盲目oF畹牧T
to understand what is really happening.
@\作棒球大盟的人
And this leads people who run Major League Baseball teams
e`估了自己的球T和伍
to misjudge their players and mismanage their teams.
真是抱歉
I apologize.
^mf
Go on.
好 I棒球俱凡康哪切┤ 思S是Iu球T
Okay. People who run ball clubs, they think in terms of buying players.
你的目的不是Iu球T 而是I取倮
Your goal shouldn't be to buy players. Your goal should be to buy wins.
要I到倮 就要I得分
And in order to buy wins, you need to buy runs.
你想找人代替尼.戴蒙
You're trying to replace Johnny Damon.
波士Dtm看中尼.戴蒙
The Red Sox see Johnny Damon
是看到一r值750f美元一年的明星
and they see a star who's worth $7.5 million a year.
而我看尼.戴蒙
When I see Johnny Damon,
我看到的是...
what I see is...
θ绾蔚梅趾o概念的球T
an imperfect understanding of where runs come from.
他是不e的守潢T
The guy's got a great gloVe.
是很好的首l打者 他很I
He's a decent leadoff hitter. He can steal bases.
但他值波士Dtmo的 每年750f的薪金
But is he worth the $ 7.5 million a year that the Boston Red Sox are paying him?
不 不值
No. No.
棒球的思S在中世o水平
Baseball thinking is medieVal.
他的想法都有}
They are asking all the wrong questions.
如果我@痈嬖Ve人 我就是反优 冒天下之大不t
And if I say it to anybody, I'm ostracized. I'm a leper.
所以我才跟你@圈子
So that's why I'm cagey about this with you.
所以我...
That's why...
我尊敬你 e恩先生 如果你想掏心C的
I respect you, Mr. Beane, and if you want full disclosure,
我X得你放掉戴蒙是件好事
I think it's a good thing that you got Damon off your payroll.
我X得@砗芏嘤腥さ目赡苄
I think it opens up all kinds of interesting possibilities.
- 你家l是哪 皮特 - RYm
Where you from, Pete? Maryland.
- 你在哪Y上W - 耶 我在耶上W
Where'd you go to school? Yale. I went to Yale.
- 你W什N的 - W
What'd you study? Economics.
我W的
I studied economics.
耶 W 有棒球
Yale, economics and baseball.
你很有意思 Pete
You're funny, Pete.
告V我 槭颤N是比利
Tell me, why Billy?
是什N他f而出
What is it that makes him special?
很y遇到比利@拥哪贻p人
Very rare do you come upon a young man like Billy
能跑 能守 能投 能打
who can run, who can field, who can throw, who can hit,
能舫龊们
and who can hit with power.
@五N技能R 不多的
Those five tools, you don't see that very often.
我中意的^大部分年px手
Most of the youngsters that we have an interest in
擅L一或身技能
have one or two tools,
我希望他能多l展一
and we're hoping to develop an extra one.
而你的鹤游屙全能
Your son has five.
我在榧~s找一未淼某巨星
We're looking at a guy that's a potential superstar for us in New York.
F在是r候他起w了
The time is now to get him started.
我浜昧厚的待遇
We're prepared to make a sizable financial commitment.
大都全力支持比利
The Mets are gonna stand behind Billy
因槲期望他成 大盟Y的中鍪
because we expect him to be our big-league center fielder.
@支票代表了~s大都
This check here represents the offer
o比利的S厚回
that the New York Mets would be making to Billy.
你知道他已得到了 斯坦福大W的全~W金
You do know that he's been accepted to Stanford on a full scholarship?
我知道
I do.
所以他能擅婕骖了
So he can do both?
很不幸的 他不能同r 上斯坦福和I棒球
Unfortunately, he can't do Stanford and professional baseball.
他必有所取
He would have to pick one or the other.
如果要大都的中鍪
If he wants to be center fielder for the Mets,
一名棒球\T
wants to be a baseball player,
他必⒋俗槿松第一位的事I和I
he really needs to accept this as life's first occupation, first career.
某r刻有人告V我 不能再玩小孩子的[蛄
We're all told at some point we can no longer play the children's game.
只是我不清楚是什Nr刻
We just don't know when that's gonna be.
有些人18q就到 有些人40q才知道 但有那r候
Some of us are told at 18, some of us are told at 40, but we're all told.
@是一生一次的C遇
But this is a once-in-a-lifetime opportunity.
我很看好你 而@PX的的 充分表_了我的渴望
We want you badly, and we think that this amount of money expresses that desire.
比利 @是你的x 不^o你怎NQ定
Billy, this is your decision, and whatever that decision is,
我和你都]有意
you know it's fine with your mother and I.
- 喂 - 嘿 我是比利 e恩
Hello? Hey, it's Billy Beane.
- F在c啊 - 我不知道
Hey, what time is it? I don't know.
著 第一x秀你挑我
Listen, would you have drafted me in the first round?
什N
What?
我x_之後 你在X上查^我
After I left, you looked me up on your computer.
第一x秀你挑我岚
Would you have drafted me in the first round?
的 你是好球手
I did, yeah. You were a good player.
e胡扯 夥
Cut the crap, man.
第一x秀你挑我岚
Would you have drafted me in the first round?
我把你排到第九 ]有s金
I'd haVe taken you in the ninth round. No signing bonus.
我猜你放 接受斯坦福的W金
I imagine you would'Ve passed and taken that scholarship.
]e
Yeah.
打包吧 皮特
Pack your bags, Pete.
我目死夫m印第安手上I了你
I just bought you from the Cleveland Indians.
- @是B著那A子 -  我斫忾_
Is it attached to that clamp? Yeah, let me unhook it.
哪茄Y滑下
Slide it up right there.
- 到左 - 我是啊
To the left. I did.
- 好 好 - 等等 有c
Yeah, yeah. Hang on, it's wet.
放吧
Come on.
- 早安 K珊 咖啡好了 -
Morning, Suzanne. Coffee on? Yes.
很好
Great.
- 比利.e恩k公室 - 嘿
Billy Beane's office. Hey.
- 皮特.布m德 - 比利
Peter Brand. Billy.
- 你好…嗨 你好 - 到你真_心
How are...? Hi, how you doing? Nice to see you.
你能碚婧 你幼髡婵彀
Good to have you here. Boy, you move in fast.
我今早到的
Yeah, yeah. I got here early this morning.
Wow. Huh.
- 都搬好了 - 不e
All moved in. Yeah.
是啊
Yeah.
嗨 比利
Hey, Billy,
我希望你看看
I wanted you to see these player evaluations
你要我做的球Tu估
that you asked me to do.
我要你u估三
I asked you to do three.
Yeah.
- u估三球T - 是啊
To evaluate three players. Yeah.
你做了
How many did you do?
Forty-seven.
不e
Okay.
其是51 我不知道才槭颤N撒e
Actually, 51. I don't know why I lied just then.
你陪我去分牌下走走吧
Why don't you walk me through the board?
xx
Thank you.
用左上角的@方程式
Using this equation in the upper left,
我J槲至少需要A99霰荣
I'm projecting that we need to win at least 99 games
才能打入季後
in order to make it to the postseason.
要A@N多 我至少拿下814分
We need to score at least 814 runs in order to win those games
最多只能645分
and allow no more than 645 runs.
@是什N
What's this?
是我做的年度球Tu估t
This is a code that I'Ve written for our year-to-year projections.
是根我掌握的所有 YηTM行u估
This is building in the intelligence that we haVe to project players.
然後呢
Okay.
就是⒏鞣N信息底只
It's about getting things down to one number.
通^我特有的分析
Using the stats the way we read them,
就lFe人看不到的 球T的在r值
we'll find Value in players that nobody else can see.
有的人才因
People are oVerlooked
各N偏和外在的缺c被忽
for a Variety of biased reasons and perceiVed flaws.
比如年g 外貌 性格
Age, appearance, personality.
比.詹姆斯\用W摒@些因素
Bill James and mathematics cut straight through that.
比利 在我u估的2f球T中
Billy, of the 20,000 notable players for us to consider,
我相信就有我付得起的25
I believe that there is a championship team
可以M建一支Z冠的球T
of 25 people that we can afford,
因槠渌I热耸慷嫉凸懒怂
because everyone else in baseball undervalues them.
他就像被孤立的不匹配玩具
Like an island of misfit toys.
比利 @是查德.布拉德福 他是後援投手
Billy, this is chad Bradford. He's a relief pitcher.
他就是最被低估的球T之一
He is one of the most undervalued players in baseball.
他的缺c是投球幼骱芑稽
His defect is that he throws funny.
就因樗幼骰稽 棒球大盟]人看重他
Nobody in the big leagues cares about him because he looks funny.
如果在我手上 @砘⒉恢皇亲罴淹妒
This guy could be not just the best pitcher in our pen,
而成樗有棒球比中 最牛的後援投手
but one of the most effectiVe relief pitchers in all baseball.
@人值得年薪300f美金
This guy should cost $3 million a year.
我出23f7就能下他
We can get him for 237,000.
比利
Billy.
- 就是@ - 是
That it? Yeah.
嗨 艾特
Hey, Art.
可以在你_前和你
Can I talk to you before you get started?
- 我F在有c忙 - 我知道
I'm a bit busy right now. I know.
- 我知道 - 好吧
I know. Okay.
- 大家早上好 - 艾特
Morning, everyone. Art.
- 皮特.布m德 很高d到你 - 皮特死哪喝チ
Peter Brand. Nice to meet you. Where the hell's Pete?
@位是皮特
That's Pete.
找座位 我R上回
Grab a seat. I'll be right back.
行了 你f他在哪碇
All right, where did you say he's at?
嗯 他在...
Okay. He's on...
- 那小子是l - 是我朋友
Who's the kid? A friend of mine.
只一年合同 我]法指н@支
I can't manage this team under a one-year contract.
你然可以
Well, sure you can.
不 我不行
No, I can't.
好吧 我要拉一去比
Okay. I gotta put a team on the field.
之後 我仔看看你的合同
After that, I'll take a good long look at your contract.
先和球理s 然後再M①怎N
Deal with the manager's contract, then put a team on the field.
艾特 F在如果地L球被舻揭 ]人接得住
At this moment, if a grounder's hit to first, nobody's there to stop it.
在只一年合s的毫ο 治疫@份活可不容易
It's not easy doing what I do under the cloud of a one-year contract.
行了 我能理解
Okay, I understand that.
- 我也有^@Nv - 我知道 我知道你也有^
I've been there. I know you have.
一年合sηT和 球理意味著同拥毫
A one-year contract means the same thing to a manager as to a player.
我]有信心
There's not a lot of faith there.
上季A了102 有@拥慕Y果真是奇怪
Which is strange after a 102-win season.
明白了
I see.
你要是了季最後那鲎钪匾的 前面的倮就]人在乎了
If you lose the last game of the season, nobody gives a shit.
- @NfF在任在我了 - 不 艾特 是我的任
So it's on me now? No, Art, it's on me.
@小伙是新淼慕理助理
And the kid is the new assistant GM.
- 好吧 - 行了 各位
Okay. Okay, fellas.
嗨 比利
Hey, Billy.
你不能否J他的攻袅 他有一手
You can't deny his offensive output. He can play.
我需要打球的人
And we need people that can play.
你想先l
Who do you wanna talk about first?
一都不想
None of them.
比利 我差38本敬 和120打c
Billy, we got 38 home runs, 120 RBIs to make up for.
各位 你是在找人取代吉安比
Guys, you're still trying to replace Giambi.
我告V^你我做不到 我不能@N干
I told you we can't do it, and we can't do it.
F在我能做的是再造一他
Now, what we might be able to do is re-create him.
- 在瞪显僭焖 - 在什N上
Re-create him in the aggregate. The what?
吉安比的上韭适.477
Giambi's on-base percentage was.477.
戴蒙是.324 W梅多是.291
Damon's on-base, .324. And Olmedo's was.291.
加起硎...
Add that up and you get...
你是要我f
Do you want me to speak?
我指著你的r候 是的
When I point at you, yeah.
- 1.092 - 除以3
1.092. Divided by three.
- .364 - @就是我要的
.364. That's what we're looking for.
三球T 三平均上韭适...
Three ballplayers... Three ballplayers whose average OBP is...
.364
.364.
- 慢著 @N算不 - ]e的 阿迪
Wait, that doesn't come out right. It's right, Artie.
- 比利 - 你要加上@
Billy. You gotta carry the one.
- 比利 - 把@去掉
Billy. Scratch this out.
什N
Yeah?
那是l
Who's that?
那是皮特
That's Pete.
@Y需要皮特
Does Pete really need to be here?
需要
Yes, he does.
好了 @些就是我要的人
Okay, here's who we want.
1: 苌的弟弟 苋鹈
Jason's little brother, Jeremy.
- 天啊 - 比利 @可有麻
Oh, God. Billy, that's trouble.
比利 如果我...我能插一句 他的}在鐾
Billy, look, if l... Yeah. Billy, if I may, he's had his problems off the field,
而且我知道他在錾系娜觞c
and we know what he can't do on the field.
他都_始l福了
He's getting thick around the waist.
有蟮勒f他吸大麻 出入衣舞俱凡
There's reports about him on weed, in strip clubs.
他的上韭示褪俏F在要找的
His on-base percentage is all we're looking at now.
相於他那28.5f的身r 苋鹈椎纳韭在很可^
And Jeremy gets on base an awful lot for a guy who only costs 285,000.
- 天呢 比利... - 2
Jeez, Billy... Number two:
- 大l.Z斯蒂斯 - 哦 不要吧
David Justice. Oh, no.
- 他的腿]用了 - @主意很
His legs are gone. Not a good idea.
- 老人Z斯蒂斯? - 怎N@Nf
Old Man Justice? Why is that?
施泰因布{於他的退步很怒 他情o`s金⑺逐出
Steinbrenner's so pissed at his decline, he's willing to eat his contract to get rid of him.
- f得好 - 十年前 大l.Z斯蒂斯的名字的
Exactly. Ten years ago, Justice, big name.
⒓恿撕芏嘀匾事
Been in big games.
季初⑹俏的票房大u狳c
He's gonna really help our season tickets early in the year,
但到了七八月的三伏天 他可以保持w重我就走\了
but in the dog days in July, August, we're lucky if he's gonna hit his weight.
比利 他腿都]用了 他是防守的累
Billy, his legs are gone, and he's a defensive liability.
我都岩伤的羟蛩偈遣皇窃诮≡
I question whether the bat speed's there.
- 他的腿]用了 - 格雷迪
His legs are gone. Grady.
他能上60霰荣就很走\了 你看中他什N了
We'll be lucky to get 60 games out of him. Why do you like him?
因樗上韭矢
Because he gets on base.
- @算什N - 我在致
What is this? What are we doing?
好了 三
Okay, number three:
- 斯科特.哈特伯格 - l
Scott Hatteberg. Who?
- 哈特伯格？ - 正是
Hatteberg? Exactly.
他起砭拖袷W克m\蛹谊球T
He sounds like an Oakland A already.
- ]e 他有c小}... - 小}? 他不能扔球
Yes, he's had a little problem with... Little problem? He can't throw.
他的羟蚵适.260 他的IS金期已Y束了
He's a career.260 hitter. The best part of his career is over.
- 我f才要_始 - 波士D不想要他了
It's just getting started. Boston wants to cut him.
- 可]人想他回去 - @ξ是好事 他很便宜
No one wants to pick him up. Good. He's cheap.
我把事情搞清楚 你要一
Let me get this straight. You're gonna get a guy
被半蛋羟蚵盟球放的人
that's been released by half the organizations in baseball
因樗的肘部受^不可治K的 神pе滤不能扔球
because he's got nonrepairable nerve damage in his elbow and can't throw.
他不能扔球又不能接防 他能致锬
He can't throw and he can't field. But what can he do?
各位
Oh, boy.
查查你的Y料 否t我就皮特了
Check your reports or I'm gonna point at Pete.
- 他能上 - 他能上
He gets on base. He can get on base.
- 他是保送次刀喟 - 他上敬刀 洛克
So he walks a lot. He gets on base a lot, Rocco.
我需要在乎是保送是安打
Do I care if it's a walk or a hit?
皮特
Pete?
- 你不需要 - 我不需要
You do not. I do not.
比利我有37比@三砘 更好的自由球T
I got 37 free agents that are better than those three guys.
等一下 我再搞明白了
Wait a minute, let me get this straight.
就是f榱颂Q吉安比
So you're not gonna bring in one
你要下不止一 而是三次品球T
but three defective players to replace Giambi?
你不是相信了比.詹姆斯 那套鬼了吧
You're not buying into this Bill James bullshit?
@是W克m\蛹谊的新方向
This is the new direction of the A's.
我是桌上的算牌客
We are card counters at the blackjack table
我要A^f家
and we're gonna turn the odds on the casino.
- 我不懂 - f到^ 夥
I don't see it. Seriously, guys.
我想我需要住 他是我的ь^人
I think we have to remember this is the man.
他只需ν顿Y人和上帝
He answers to no one except ownership and God.
他]必要ξ有交待
And he doesn't have to answer to us.
我提建h 他碜Q定
We make suggestions, he makes decisions.
既然@诱f 我榱 @俱凡扛好
That's all fine and well, but we've been working our asses off
I心r血了六半周 你s不屑一
for weeks to make this club better, and you're shitting all over it.
@不是在
This is not a discussion.
那我在f什N
What are we discussing?
瑞 不是
Barry, not a discussion.
比利 夥
Billy, man, um,
我想你忘了一件事
there's one thing you're forgetting.
@三人都不知道怎N守一
None of those three guys knows how to play first base.
你得教他中的一
Well, you're gonna have to teach one of them.
教?
Teach?
教哪
Which one?
@是西雅D市^度假季的重^
This is really the kickoff to the holiday season here in downtown Seattle.
@盛事已I淞字 但一切等待都是值得的
It took weeks of planning to lead up to the big event, but it was well worth it.
天夂O了 人玩得高d
The weather was ideal. People are still haVing a great time.
成千上f的人早早就出T了
Thousands of people were out earlier.
正在槟悴蟮氖
We haVe a nice recap for you
在西雅D市中心e行的盛事
of all the great events taking place downtown in Seattle...
- 喂 - 斯科特
Hello? Scott?
是我
Yes.
- 我是W克m\蛹谊的比利.e恩 - 你好
It's Billy Beane of the Oakland A 's. Yes.
- 可以 - 然
Can we talk? Uh, yeah.
你能我M
Do you wanna let us in?
- 你f什N - 我就在外面
Pardon me? We're out front.
- 什N - 在路
What? On the curb.
哦 好的 好的
Uh, yeah, yeah.
H鄣
Honey?
xx xx 夫人
Oh, thank you. Thank you, ma'am.
真客
Very kind.
手肘好些了 斯科特
How's the elbow, Scott?
挺好 很好 好O了
You know, it's good. It's really good. It's great. Uh...
- 我根本扔不了球 - 知道
I can't throw the ball at all. Yeah.
你最後一次扔球是谋景遽崦
You've thrown your last ball from behind home plate.
我就想@Nf
That's what I'd say. Well...
好消息是 我要你守一
Good news is, we want you at first.
我想要你W克m\蛹谊的一臼
We want you to play first base for the Oakland A's.
@...
Okay, well,
我只^捕手
I've only ever played catcher.
斯科特 你再也不是捕手了
Scott, you're not a catcher anymore.
如果你是 我就不是 唯一o你打的人了
If you were, our call wouldn't have been the only one you got.
-  著 我很感激你的P注 - 不用x
Yeah. Hey, listen, no, I appreciate it. You're welcome.
- 但}是... - 你不知道怎N守一
But the thing is, is... You don't know how to play first base.
- 斯科特 - ]e
Scott. That's right.
]那Ny的 斯科特
It's not that hard, Scott.
- 告V他 A叔 - 是非常y
Tell him, Wash. It's incredibly hard.
任何有意x的事都不容易 我教你的
Hey, anything worth doing is. And we're gonna teach you.
等一下 我是f 那...
Wait a minute here. I mean, but what about...?
苌走了 斯科特
Jason's gone, Scott.
你想要我取代吉安比的一疚
You want me to take Giambi's spot at first base?
- ]e - 球迷怎Nf
Yeah. What about the fans?
- 也S我也能教教他 - 球迷不...f得好
Maybe I can teach one of them. The fans don't... Good one.
我的俱凡坎皇怯汕蛎越I
Fans don't run my ball club.
你怎N醒了
Honey, what are you doing awake?
H鄣 麻┠...
Sweetheart, can you?
那是我女
That's my daughter.
你有孩子
You got kids?
有 一女
Uh, yeah, a daughter.
斯科特 @是W克m\蛹谊打球的合s
Scott, this is a contract to play ball for the Oakland A's.
送了副本o你的o人
A copy's been sent over to your agent.
和你妻子商量一下 告V我Y果
Discuss with your wife, let us know.
xx
Thank you.
再
Bye-bye. Bye.
- 哦 α 斯科特 - 嗯？
Oh, and, Scott. Yeah?
不要告V任何人一镜氖虑
Don't tell anyone about the first-base thing.
好的 先生
Yes, sir. Okay.
- 假期愉快 - 好的
Happy holidays. All right.
- 嗨 莎 - 你好 比利
Hey, Sharon. Hi, Billy.
- 她浜昧 - 她和朋友出去了
Is she ready? She's out with friends.
但她R上回 M戆
But she'll be back. Come in.
- 好的 - 她就在@ 等等
Okay. Yeah, she's right here. Hold on.
o你
Here you go.
- 坐 - 好的
Here, wanna have a seat? Yeah.
- 你好 比利 - 挺好 你呢 艾
You good, Billy? Yeah. How are you, Alan?
挺好 真的挺好 @地方很安o
Good. Really good. Things are peaceful around here.
到你真好
It's good to see you.
xx 艾
Thanks, Alan.
季Y束後我就]^你了
I haven't got to see you since play-offs.
我得f~s是心地
I wanted to say that New York was heartbreaking.
δ愣言肯定如此
I'm sure for you too.
]字球能拼到那 看到你打M去了 真是...
Not many teams make it that far, and to watch you go that far was...
- _值貌诲e - xx褒
It was really an accomplishment. Well, that's nice.
球涞迷觞N恿
How is the team shaping up?
- 不e 正在重M - 很好啊
Team's good. Rebuilding. Good.
我看蠹上f你失去了吉安搏比和戴蒙
I read you lost Giambonni and Damon.
- 是吉安比 - 吉安比
Giambi. Giambi.
]e 有戴蒙和伊斯林豪森
Yeah. Damon, Isringhausen.
- 他真的...走了? - 走了 不是新r事了
They're really...? They're gone? Gone. Yesterday's news.
- 那太可怕了 - ]有啦 但形莸拇_谰
That's terrible. No, but that is a tough situation.
真是...
That's...
不^你好起淼 你能把事情搞定
You're gonna be fine, though. You always figure something out.
- 她到哪 - 在街^是
Where is she? Where was she? Down the street or?
Σ黄  我打了她手C 她正要上山
Oh, sorry, yeah. I just talked to her on her cell. She's coming up the hill.
好吧
Okay.
她有手C了?
She's got a cell phone?
- 是的 - 12q就配手C?
Yeah. A 12-year-old?
是的
Yeah.
哈
Huh.
以防f一
For emergencies.
家L的重大Q定
Big parenting decision.
但那是...我...那 我一起的事
But it's something that, you know, we, you know, all should discuss,
如果你有任何反σ庖...
because if you have any objections, of course...
我和她商量的
Her mother and I will discuss it.
但xx你
But thank you.
有喜g的
Any of these? Um...
我不知道
I don't know.
@不e
Do you...? This one's cool.
好是不好啊
Is that good or bad?
- 蝴蝶 - 看起聿诲e
Butterflies. They're okay.
看 那好看 我喜gt色的
Look, that one's pretty. I like the red.
我?
Should we try?
不要
No?
- 我喜g@ - 是
Oh, I like this one. Yeah?
爸爸 你看@
Dad, look at this one.
- 看它的t色 - 真漂亮
Look how it's red. It's beautiful.
- @好看 - 我碓
This one's pretty. Let's try it out.
就在@
Just right here? Why don't we go over there?
去那好
Can we go over there?
Lenka 「The Show」
H鄣 你唱出戆 唱得那N好
Oh, honey, you need to sing. That's so good.
真好
That's beautiful.
我有r也唱
Sometimes I sing.
唱歌很有意思 但我不想e人到我唱歌
It's fun to sing with your song, but I don't want people to listen to me.
H鄣 我想人 喜g你唱的 很好
Well, honey, I think people would love to listen to you. That's beautiful.
可以榘职殖一小段
Would you sing a little for your dad?
就在@Y 商店Y
Right here in the middle of the store?
- 就唱拙 - 就拙
Little bit. Little bit.
- 浜昧 - 好了
You ready? I'm ready.
好吧
Okay.
* 我有c左右呻y *
* I'm just a little bit Caught in the middle *
* 生活是座迷m 凼i *
* Life is a maze And love is a riddle *
* 我不知道去哪 我o法自完成 我努力了 *
* I don't know where to go Can't do it alone, I've tried *
* 我不知道槭颤N *
* And I don't know why *
* 我只是迷失在此刻的小女孩 *
* I'm just a little girl Lost in the moment *
* 管害怕但我s不流露 *
* I'm so scared But I don't show it *
* 我]有k法 快被艨 *
* I can't figure it out It's bringing me down *
* 我知道我得放手 *
* I know I've got to let it go *
* 好好享受@鲂 *
* And just enjoy the show **
比利.e恩第一x秀就@x
Billy Beane was taken in the first round of the amateur draft.
1984年
我想有人要把比利.e恩走
I think this is a steal, to get Billy Beane.
他年p 有才能
He's young, he's talented.
一速度型的五全能球T 他是不容e^的力股
A true fiVe-tool player with speed. This guy is a can't-miss prospect.
@~s大都碚f是很好的E象
This is a great sign for the new York Mets.
f不定就是他一直在で蟮霓DC
And it could be the turnaround that they'Ve been looking for.
那
Ball one.
我看好比利.e恩
I'll take Billy Beane oVer Strawberry.
比利.e恩做了有意思的x 他拒^了W金
Billy Beane, an interesting pick, turned down a scholarship.
他本砜梢匀ニ固垢４W
He could'Ve gone to Stanford.
有r你要到了大盟才明白
Sometimes you don't find out till you get to the big leagues...
好球
Strike!
@砘]有失∵^ 他高中I
This guy has never failed at anything. He's coming out of high school.
比利本硪去上大W 他可以成橐幻出色的橄烨蛩姆中l
Billy was gonna go to college. He could'Ve been a great quarterback.
三振出局
Strike three.
任何一棒球球
There's not an organization in baseball
都意把涸谶@年p人身上
who would not haVe taken a chance on this young guy.
1985年
他]成功 每年都有@拥睦子
He didn't pan out. That happens every year.
有些成功 有些失×
Some do, some don't.
我是f 如果你@Q定不_定...
I mean, if you're haVing any doubt at all about this...
1986年
1987年
P於W金的...
HaVing the scholarship...
你鹤佑刑熨x
Your son was born with a God-giVen ability.
很少有球探能探知一年p人的想法
Few scouts can go into the mind of a young man
砼嗨是否真的ψ约旱哪芰τ行判
and determine whether he's really confident about what he can do.
一很特e的球T
A Very special player.
所以你可以根他的能力s
So you can sign him based on his ability,
之後他就得成功得自信起
but then he's gotta be successful to be confident.
1988年
他一旦有了自信 你就有盼^了
And once he becomes confident, that's when you'Ve got something.
1989年
你根眼的做出Q定
You make a decision on what you see.
如果不成功 你就得往前看
And if things don't pan out, you moVe on.
@就是棒球
That's baseball.
很多人到了召 那能被x中的s是e
Many are called, few are chosen.
比利 @是P文.尤克Y斯 被Q^「希D保送之神」 （尤克力斯是希D名 他上韭O高）
Billy, that is Kevin Youkilis. That is the Greek God of Walks.
他是我的偶像
That's my hero.
他得到的保送上敬 是除了瑞.邦以外
That man gets walked more than anybody in baseball
最多的
except for Barry Bonds.
去年6月我Df服史派_下他
I tried to convince Shapiro to pick him up last June,
但他f他走路u[像只子
but he said he waddled like a duck.
Y果波士D走了他
Yeah, Boston snagged him.
我想他是想^望一下
I think they wanna wait and see.
- 你好 比利 - 比利
Are you okay, Billy? Billy?
我可以
Can we talk?
可以 好的
Yeah. Yeah.
你不_心 格雷迪 怎N了
You're unhappy, Grady. Why?
哇
Wow.
- 我可以直直f - 然 f吧
May I speak candidly? Sure, go ahead.
全美I棒球大盟和它的粉z 很芬獍涯愫凸雀栊∽
Major League Baseball and its fans, they're gonna be more than happy
扔到巴士下
to throw you and Google Boy under the bus
如果你照目前@有惺碌脑
if you keep doing what you're doing.
你不能用X去M
You don't put a team together with a computer.
- 不能 - 不能
No? No.
棒球不只是底 不是一T科W
Baseball isn't just numbers. It's not science.
如果是的 任何人都能做我的工作 但其他做不到
If it was, anybody could do what we're doing, but they can't.
他不知道我所知的
They don't know what we know.
他]有我的和直X
They don't have our experience and our intuition.
好吧
Okay.
你就靠那有耶大W WW位的小孩
You got a kid in there that's got a degree in economics from Yale.
你面前t是有29年棒球的球探
You got a scout here with 29 years of baseball experience.
你xe了⒅\ο
You're listening to the wrong one.
有些y以捉摸的因素只有刃胁哦
Now, there are intangibles that only baseball people understand.
你要低估球探干了150年的活路
You're discounting what scouts have done for 150 years?
甚至包括你自己
Even yourself?
mh境 否t死路一l
Adapt or die.
@是因槟阕约旱慕v 是不是
This is about you and your shit, isn't it?
20年前 有球探看e人了
Twenty years ago, some scout got it wrong.
- 哇 行了 行了 - 你F在是向鹘y正式宣鹆
Whoa. Okay. Okay. Now you declare war on the system.
好了 好了 我f删淞 你]有水晶球
Okay, okay, my turn. You don't have a crystal ball.
要看著一人就能Ay他的未 你的本事也不比我多少
You can't look at a kid and predict his future any more than I can.
我和你一起坐在那些餐桌
I've sat at those kitchen tables with you
你跟家Lf 「到r候了我自然就知道」
and listened to you tell parents, "When I know, I know.
「你的鹤有胁恍 我一眼就能看出怼
And when it comes to your son, I know."
其你做不到
And you don't.
你做不到
You don't.
好了 我才不在乎什N友情
Okay. I don't give a shit about friendship,
不管F在 是那
this situation, or the past.
全美I棒球大盟和我思路一致 你不A的
Major League Baseball thinks the way I think. You're not gonna win.
我要o你一免M建h
And I'll give you a nickel's worth of free advice.
在你我⒓油赀@K〉馁季 K被老_除後
You're never gonna get another job
你⒃僖舱也坏焦ぷ
after this catastrophic season you're about to set us all up for.
你⒉坏貌幌蚰愕暮⒆咏忉
You'll have to explain to your kid
你槭颤N在迪克\佑闷返旯ぷ
why you're working at Dick's Sporting Goods.
我不炒你~的 格雷迪
I'm not gonna fire you, Grady.
- 操你的 比利 - F在我_了你
Fuck you, Billy. Now I will.
祝你好\ 艾特
Good luck, Art.
久保田 你]打^棒球
Kubota. You never played ball, right?
- 打^一c少年棒球 - 你懋首席球探
I played a little T-ball. You're the new head scout.
恭喜
Congratulations.
所以波士D正在^望？
So Boston's gonna wait and see?
Yeah.
就你和我 皮特
Yeah. It's just you and me, Pete.
我_始吧
And we're all in.
春季
起砗孟衲阍樗的行榈狼
It sounds like you're apologizing for what they're doing.
我]有 我只是不明白
I'm not. I just don't know what you're gonna do
你能用\蛹谊的 A算做什N 你Il
with the budget that the A 's haVe. Who are you gonna get?
我看了春季的名
I'm looking at the spring-training roster.
- 你直在_玩笑 - 怎N了
You gotta be kidding me. How so?
他在那壕拖小丑
He looked like a clown out there.
- l - 查德.布拉德福
Who? Chad Bradford.
布拉德福情r如何
Tell me about Bradford.
我挺喜g他的 不^他不是外行
I like him a little bit, but he's a specialist.
你不可能_他f "第八局就看你的了
He's not a guy that you say, "The eighth inning is yours,
左撇子τ移沧"
lefties Vs. Righties."
@是我的看法
In my opinion.
我不知道比利.e恩和 管理邮窃觞N看他的
I don't know what Billy Beane and management understands about him.
但他的投球r速只有82 83a 得有ce的…
He only throws the ball about 82, 83 miles an hour. There must be something...
他是怪胎 @可不是在F他
He is a freak, and not in a good way.
我你
Let me ask you this.
如果想在分^Y@
Talking about trying to win a diVision.
我指望大l刀未老
We're counting on DaVid to be the guy he was.
但我有c岩 他已老了
I haVe my doubts. He's gotten old.
所以他不在~s 也不在克利夫m 他o可去
That's why he's not in new York anymore, not in cleveland anymore.
我本o尼.戴蒙的X so了@U物
We paid him the money we should'Ve been giVing to Johnny Damon.
苋鹈.吉安比
Hey. Jeremy Giambi.
他才是我要心的人
That's the one to worry about.
他去城的rg比在W克m更多
He gets comps up and down Vegas more than in Oakland.
@你警醒啊
That should tell you something right there.
到底要@些砘致锇
Isn't that the deal with these guys?
他就W光了一年
He has one good year.
然後得到一PS厚的身r 接著就被D
And he gets a huge offer and then he gets traded.
- U勃 加力 - 哈特伯格
Bob. Harder. Hatteberg.
好 很好
Good. Good.
比利 我得哈特伯格的事
Billy, we haVe to talk about Hatteberg.
- f吧 - 他在一具是]感X
Go. There's just no feel for the spot.
我X得他x大盟一臼 有很L距x
I think it's a long shot that he can be a big-league first baseman.
@才是第一周第一天 你不能就喽了
It's day one of the first week. You can't judge this yet.
不 我X得我可以喽了
No, I think we can judge it.
我喜g他 你知道 不^我是可以喽
I mean, I like him, you know, but I can judge him.
一λ碚fb不可及
First base is the moon to him.
吉安比就]被看臭啊 吉安比初是最差的一臼至
It wasn't to Giambi. Giambi's the worst first baseman in baseball.
- 你拿他跟吉安比比 - f什N呢
Gonna compare him to Giambi? What are we talking about?
好吧
All right.
你X得呢 A叔
What do you think, Wash?
f好c是他缺乏自信
The nice way to say it is he lacks confidence.
那就o他自信
Well, give him some.
我的 不^我有佩{ 他能打一
I'll do that, but we got Pena, who can play first.
而且他B很好
And he's looking mighty good out there.
就用哈特
We wanna go with Hattie.
有六周rg
We got six weeks.
用心c
Get down in it.
- 很好 - 斯科特.H
There you go. Scotty H.
- 就是@ - 烨蚝檬职
That's what I'm talking about. Picking machine.
就是棒球而已
It's only baseball.
@事最好行得通
This better work.
逗你的啦
I'm just kidding you.
* Don't stop belieVin' *
上啊 W克m
Let's go, Oakland!
* Streetlight **
- @|西怎N回事 - 要一美元 哥
What is wrong with this thing? It's a dollar, man.
- 什N - g迎W克m D.J
What? Welcome to Oakland, D.J.
真是搞笑
Oh, you gotta be shitting me.
我想今年的比 C明F才倮
I think this year, we're gonna show that it takes a team to win,
而不是靠某人 是F
not any individual guy, just a team.
我X得我很
And I think we got a hell of a ball club here.
查德 你今天X得有毫
Chad, are you intimidated at all today?
不能f有毫 真的 我就是挺d^的 就像你f的
I wouldn't say I'm intimidated, really. I'm just really excited, like you said.
苋鹈.吉安比 ]有了你哥哥苌 @支球要如何取
Jeremy, how's the team gonna fare without your brother, Jason?
就目前碚f 球找到了新人填a空缺
Well, you know, the organization did a great job
做得挺成功的
of bringing in good young guys to fill that role.
f \蛹沂潜阋rI到的你
Let's face it, they're getting a deal with you.
洋基s高rI了苌
The Yankees are paying Jason a lot of money.
你在@Y的酬谥挥心屈Nc 你感受怎
You are coming here on a dime. How does that make you feel?
我感X很好 呃...
I feel good. Um...
- 你手指的情r如何 - 就那
How are the nerves in your fingers? You know.
我ff年g吧 你36q了
Gotta start with the age, 36 years old.
你X得自己的身w 能芜^一季
How do you think your body's gonna hold up?
你在衣舞吧和狂g上花了大把rg
You spend a lot of time at strip clubs, partying.
你υ鱿率艿降年P注X得琅
Do you resent the attention you get off the field?
不啊 我喜g
I love it.
- 你常在城打混 - 是的
You spend a lot of time in Vegas. I do.
- 我感X很好 就像我f的 做了很多洹 - 抱歉 你e踔我的R^
I feel great. I did a lot of work to get... Excuse me. Get out of my shot.
抱歉 f
Sorry, go ahead.
於我的年g
There have been questions about my age
和所^的技能下滑 你有很多疑 不^我C明自己的
and my declining skills, some say, but I'm here to prove that wrong.
我是你百分百_定
I asked if you were 100 percent.
- 抱歉 e恩先生 - 嗨 查德
Excuse me, Mr. Beane? Hey, Chad.
- 我]打_你吧 - ]有 怎N了
Hey, I'm not disturbing you, am I? Not at all. What's up?
我想感x你o我@C
I wanted to say thank you for this opportunity.
很高d你能成槲的T 我都@益匪\的
Well, we enjoy having you. It's gonna work out well for all of us.
我很感激 先生 ]人o我打大盟的C
I appreciate it, sir. Nobody's ever given me a chance like this before.
]有?
Nobody?
只有你 先生
Well, just you, sir.
噢 @成榇笕兆 你永h不忘的
Well, it's a big day, one you won't forget.
非常感x 我就想f
Appreciate it. And I wanna let you know
我槟愫湍愕募胰似矶\
I'm gonna be praying for you and your family.
好的
No problem.
F在xW克m\蛹谊 2002年的_只剩追昼
Well, here we are just minutes away from the season opener of 2002 for the Oakland A's.
第一局比即㈤_始
The first pitch is moments away.
奏歌r我再回
We'll come back with the national anthem.
e走_ 今天就是_幕日
Opening day is upon us.
- 好了 夥 茄子 - 好了
All right, fellas, smile. Here we go.
* Hey, she giVe me loVe And I feel all right now **
我M去了 比情用短信告V我
I'm going in. Text me the play-by-play.
什N 槭颤N
What? Why?
我不看比
I don't watch the games.
小 立定
Detail, halt!
And forward face!
首l佩{ 不是哈特伯格
@是德州游T兵今天第三支安打
That's the third Ranger batter to be hit today.
因阿v克斯._德Y格斯失` 已G煞至 第九…
Twice Alex Rodriguez was nicked. The ninth...
囊婚_始我就J真和你
I should've made you a bigger part of the conversation from day one.
你就更清楚我的
It'd be clear what we're trying to do.
@是我的e 艾特 @是我的任
That was my mistake, Art. I take responsibility for that.
你想f什N
What are you trying to say?
我要f 如果你不按用人 我怎N安排都]用
Doesn't matter what moves I make if you don't play the team the way they're designed to be.
比利 @你管不著
Billy, you're out of your depth.
- 槭颤N哈特伯格不在一 - 因樗守不了一
Why not Hatteberg at first? Because he can't play first.
- 你怎N知道 - @又不是我指У牡谝霰荣
How do you know? Not my first baseball game.
- 斯科特.哈特伯格不能打 - 他能上
Scott Hatteberg can't hit. He gets on base.
ξ碚f依然利多於弊 再A7 我的俾示统^五成了
Still keeps us in the plus column. We need to be seven over.500.
怎
What?
有什N事
Anything else?
有最後一局我想看到布拉德福投球 而不是格{迪
Yeah. I would've rather seen Bradford in the end than Magnante.
布拉福德是右手投手
Bradford's a righty.
- 我不在乎他左是右 - 我在乎
I don't care about righty-lefty. I do.
- @是因槟愕暮贤 - 不是
Could this be about your contract? No.
@有P你做你的事 我M我的
This is about you doing your job and me doing mine.
我的任是全н@支
Mine's me being left alone
你o我M建的球
to manage this team you assembled for me.
- 我不是槟憬M建的 - @然不是
I didn't assemble them for you, Art. No shit.
愉快
Good meeting.
每次我聊完
Every time we talk,
我@棒球的嵫都油然重生
I'm reinvigorated by my love of the game.
我M到了格雷迪.富森 \蛹谊前首席球探
We got Grady Fuson, former head of scouting with the Athletics.
格雷迪 你能o我解下F在的情r
And, Grady, can you interpret for us what's going on?
- 他Q之槟球 - 魔球?
They call it Moneyball. Moneyball?
@是很好的理 但就是]起作用
Yes, and it was a nice theory, and now it's just not working out.
比利.e恩M建的@支伍是基於 一叫比.詹姆斯的人建的理
Billy Beane has built this team on the ideas of a guy, Bill James,
他了一本有趣的 P於棒球yW的
who wrote an interesting book on baseball statistics.
}是比.山姆斯奈创蜻^球 也]管理^棒球
The problem is that Bill James never played, never managed.
其他只是一家i肉大豆公司的保安
He was in fact a security guard at a pork-and-beans company.
你X得@是球的末日了
Do you see this as a decimation of the organization?
我X得他是自に缆
He bought a ticket on the Titanic.
天啊
Oh, boy.
他想找新的突破
He's tried to come up with a new approach.
我λ表示尊敬 但@行不通
My hat's off to him. It won't work.
珊靡 塔哈_三振出局
One-two pitch. Tejada strikes out.
比Y束
And that is the game.
西雅D水手龆稼A了 雷
The Seattle Mariners win both games on this series, Ray.
他BmA了10 目前西雅D133
They'Ve won 10 in a row. Seattle is 13 and 3.
看不下去了
I can't watch this shit.
你跟T一起上路比
Go on the road with the team.
你]有跟他比呢
You don't go on the road with the team.
- 所以叫你去 - 你槭颤N不去
That's why I want you to do it. Why don't you?
我不能跟他有私人情x
I can't develop personal relationships with these guys.
@硬拍芎菹滦戆阉u了
I gotta be able to trade them, send them down,
甚至解雇
sometimes cut them.
@你也得WW
Which is something you should learn to do, by the way.
我永h不解雇T啊 除非你…
I would never have to cut a player, unless you...
- 拜 - 拜什N啊
Oh, come on. "Come on" what?
- 我下 - 不干
Let's practice. No.
就要 我是球T 你要解雇我
Yeah. I'm a player. You gotta cut me from the roster.
- 不 - 快
No. Go.
- 你f什N不啊 - 不
What do you mean, no? No.
- 快c - @太蠢了
Do it. This is stupid.
@是工作的一部分 夥
Part of the job, man.
好吧
Fine.
比利 坐 我要和你
Billy, please have a seat. I need to talk to you for a minute.
^m
Go on.
你一直是Y的重要成T
You've been a huge part of this team.
但有r你必要槿著想
But sometimes you have to make decisions for the team.
我想你懂的
I'm sure you can understand.
- 你要解雇我? - 非常抱歉
You're cutting me? I'm really sorry.
我在@YI了房子
I just bought a house here.
- 呃 - 就在W克m
Well... In Oakland.
唔 呃…
Well, uh... Well...
"呃... 呃..." 你就f得出@
"Well... Well..."? That's all you got to say?
我的孩子M入新W校
My kid just started a new school.
- 他交到朋友 - 那…
They made friends. That's, uh...
你不要在W期中打嗨
You shouldn't pull them out in the middle of the year.
- 你等等 - 你在f些什N鬼啊
You should wait. What the hell are you talking about?
我不知道 我]法…
I don't know. I shouldn't have...
我不@N做的 我X得@太傻了
I'm not gonna do this. I think this is stupid.
我不_除任何人 @太傻了
I'm not gonna fire anybody, and this is dumb.
他是I球T 直接告V他就是
They're professional ballplayers. Just be straight with them.
不要f扯 就f事
No fluff, just facts.
皮特 我得你x_ 芸说霓k公室
Pete, I gotta let you go. Jack's office will handle the details.
- 就@? - 卡
That's it? Pfft.
真的
Really?
你是想X袋直接中 是胸口中五流血致死?
You rather get a bullet to the head or five to the chest and bleed to death?
只有@x癜
Are those my only two options?
跟球出去比吧
Go on the road with the team.
好吧
Okay.
喂 夥
Say, bro.
- 你} - 好的
Let me ask you a question. Yeah.
你老怎N不跟球一起出T
How come your boss doesn't travel with the team?
他不喜g跟球T打成一片
He doesn't like to mingle with the players.
是榱碎_除我r不擂
Is that supposed to make us easier to cut?
我不知道 我不清楚
I don't know. I don't know.
有 槭颤N俱凡垦Y的汽水 要付一美元
And how come soda is a dollar in the clubhouse?
我]^@N事
I never seen nothing like that.
比利想把X花在球錾
Billy likes to keep the money on the field.
省汽水那cX
Soda money?
真的
Really?
我I汽水的一美元在球龅氖颤N地方呢
Where on the field is the dollar I'm paying for soda?
@是很yf清楚
It's hard to see exactly,
- 不^的_在那呢 - 嗯 是很y看到
but it's there, yeah. Yeah, it is hard to see.
我]事了
I'm done.
- 嘿 老爸 - 嗨 H鄣
Hey, Dad. Hi, honey.
- 你好 - 很好
How are you? I'm good.
- 中途簸 - 好啦
Was it bumpy? It was okay.
我依然槟泸傲
加上今晚的失 W克m\蛹谊
So with this loss tonight, the Oakland Athletics
在17霰荣Y掉了14 y以置信
incredibly, haVe lost 14 of their last 17 games.
在美西^已落後^名10俨
They are 10 games back in the American League West.
可以f失×
Is it fair to say the experiment has failed?
然 @早可A的
Well, absolutely. It was predictable.
]人希望e人失 但事[在眼前
You don't wish anybody a lack of success, but the facts are in front of you.
@不能怪艾特.哈
You can't blame Art Howe.
是的
No.
F就是 @跟y]PS @是人的比
The fact of the matter is, this is not about statistics, this is about people.
艾特.哈不是}
Art Howe is not the problem.
- 大失 - }是理室Y的比利.e恩
The problem is in the general manager's office with Billy Beane.
在我看 }的根源很明晰
The root of the problem for me is philosophical.
我之前就f了 那是想像中的棒球
I said it before. This is fantasy baseball.
比利完全]^大X思考
Billy is just not thinking.
考]Q新理 做c改
Start thinking about a new GM, making changes.
他聿豢幢荣
He never goes to the games.
@Y果@而易
This was Very predictable.
他看看錾系那r
He needs to look at what's going on.
- 他J真起砹 - 我要比利.e恩下台
The man needs to get real. I want Billy Beane gone.
e恩的X袋 有人找 你到底在想什N
Calling for Beane's head. I want your thoughts.
之前的18霰荣Y 有4霰煌攴饣蛑坏1分
The past 18 games, they'Ve been shut out or scored one run four times.
他得分太低了
They're just not scoring enough.
不光是打暨M攻的} 不是_德.波士力（教）和打者的}
It's not just the offense, not Thad Bosley and the hitters.
一切都有} 如果只是某} 可以Da救
It's everything. If there was one thing you could pick out, you'd try to fix it,
但@支完全陷入低潮
but just everything is in a funk right now.
我到底在做什N
What the hell am I doing?
天啊
Oh, man.
你看 史蒂夫
Look, Steve.
我ξ在做的事很有信心
I believe in what we're doing.
我X得不能反映 @支伍的力
The record doesn't reflect the strength of this team
也不代表季末我能@得的成
or where we're gonna be at the end of the season.
我和皮特都孕 我要^m猿衷淼姆结
Now, Pete and I here feel very strongly that we stay on the track we've chosen.
我之前的颖不 @…
Our sample size has been too small. It's too...
早 下定早
Early. It's still early.
到全明星停期前 我A期可以到什N水平
Where do we expect to be by the All-Star break?
我的目撕臀的A期
Our goal and our expectation
是到7月中和^名的俨钤7鲆
is by mid-July to be within seven games of first.
一切有好D
That would be this working.
- 到r我有Cs上 - 好得出乎意料
That keeps us in the hunt. Exceptionally well.
- 到7月 - 7月
By July. July.
那有什N阻K你 _成那目说
And what's gonna prevent you from accomplishing that?
你在心什N
What are you afraid of?
]有 所以我才在@Y 史蒂夫
Nothing. That's why we're here, Steve.
那就是我每天忙活的事 我一直在努力的
That's why we get up in the morning. That's all we do.
- 再睃c? -  再多c
More? Yeah, a little more.
- e告V - 不的
Don't tell your mother. I won't.
- 巧克力u? - 好
Chocolate sauce? Yes.
蛄
Stop.
- 要大勺子是小勺子 - 小的
Big spoon or little spoon? Little spoon.
xx
Thank you.
爸 你不G了工作吧
Dad, there's no way you're gonna lose your job, right?
什N
What?
]有啦
Well, I don't know.
- 我就是想想… - 你哪穆淼
I'm just wondering. Where'd you hear that?
我有r上W
Well, I go on the Internet sometimes.
不要 e上W
Well, don't do that. Don't go on the Internet.
e看新 e看蠹
Or watch TV or read newspapers
或是e人瞎f
or talk to people.
我不跟人聊天 就是看c|西
I don't talk to people. I just read stuff.
H鄣 一切都很好 ]}的
Honey, everything's fine. Everything's fine.
真的 你不用心
Really, you don't have to worry.
但如果你G了工作 你不是得搬走了?
But if you lose your job, will you have to move away?
甜心 我不G了工作的
Honey, I'm not gonna lose my job.
你e心
You don't have to worry.
- 好的 - 喂
Okay. Hey.
- ]}的 - 好的
There's no problem. Okay.
好 我有一堆麻 但都不是}
All right? I got uptown problems, which are not problems at all.
你不心 是吧
You're not worried, right?
- 我]心 - 好
No, I'm not worried. Okay.
是佩{
Pena.
好吧
Okay.
我要戴守右外野
I want Dye in right,
Z斯蒂斯指定代打 佩{後a
Justice DH'ing, Pena on the bench,
哈特伯格守一
Hatteberg at first,
要格作槭装l投手
and anyone but Mags first out of the pen.
你要佩{坐板凳？
You want Pena on the bench?
正是 @幽悴拍苡霉特
That's right. So you can play Hattie.
佩{不H是Y最好的一臼
Pena is not only the best first baseman,
而且是我唯一的一臼
he's the only first baseman.
哈特上韭时扰寮{高多了
Hattie gets on base more than Pena.
- H上是高20% - 但他的守淠
In fact, 20 percent more. And his fielding?
他的防守oPo要
His fielding does not matter.
- @我得蚨嗔 - 是
I've heard enough of this. Have you?
而且我…
And I, uh...
握f 我不同意
I disagree with you, plain and simple.
有 我@ш
And moreover, I'm playing my team
明年冬天述的r候才f得清楚
in a way that I can explain in job interviews next winter.
好了
Okay? Ahem.
用哈特 不要佩{
Hattie. Not Pena.
What's up, skip?
- 你怎 - 很好 你呢
How you doing? Good, how you doing, man?
昨晚睡得好
Get some sleep last night?
\蛹谊上隽 溟_始比
As the A 's hit the field, we are ready for baseball.
第一走出休息^的 是新星卡洛斯.佩{
First one out of the dugout is rookie sensation carlos Pena,
本x手Y稀有的希望 他站到了一疚恢蒙
one of the few bright lights in this lineup, taking his spot at first base.
* Down, gettin' down There's a whole lot of rhythm *
比利 一小} 你是否期望@些T有更好的…
Billy, quick question. Do you expect these guys to produce more or...?
- F在不行 夥 - 成暴跌的原因是什N
Not now. What's the reason for the slump?
* We gotta haVe the funk *
* Ow, we want the funk *
* GiVe up the funk *
* Ow, we need the funk *
* We gotta haVe the funk **
下
Get down.
球很有趣
Is losing fun?
- 球很有趣 - 不
Is losing fun? No.
那你在な颤N纷
What are you having fun for?
@起聿畔褫球
That's what losing sounds like.
你]事吧 爸爸
Are you okay, Dad?
- 你又砹 - 什N
You're doing it again. What?
你在心我
You're worrying about me.
你|底了 爸爸
You're in last place, Dad.
- 我看起n] -
Do I look worried? Yeah.
那是因槟阋坐wC @|西常往下掉
Because you're getting on an airplane, and those things crash all the time.
不要操心你老爹了
Please stop worrying about your dad.
- 都安排好了 - 好
We're all set. Okay.
- 我勰 - 我也勰
I love you. Love you too.
好了 你爸爸]}
All right. Your dad's not in trouble.
好啦
Okay.
好吧
Yeah.
- K珊 o我M艾德.f德（M城M城人理） - 好
Suzanne, get me Ed Wade. Okay.
- 咖啡好了 - 是的
Coffee on? Yes.
- 早上好 - 早上好 比利
Good morning. Good morning, Billy.
嗨 路易莎
Oh, hi, Louisa.
- 比利.e恩想c艾德.f德通 - 嗨
I need Ed Wade for Billy Beane. Hi.
稍候
Please hold.
- 什N事啊 - f德在2
What's up? Wade's on 2.
- 艾德 - 喂
Ed? Hello?
- 艾德 是我比利 - 比利 怎N了
Ed, it's Billy. Billy, what's up?
- 著 我需要找防守球T - 好的
Look, I need a little help on defense. Okay.
我意用苋鹈.吉安比斫Q
I'm willing to trade Jeremy Giambi for it.
- 真的 - 什N
Really? What?
嗯 你手^有l
Mm-hm. Who you got? What?
- 我想想 - 你致
Well, let me think. What are you doing?
清理T
Cleaning house.
- 梅布利怎 - 或S怎
Mabry? Maybe what?
- 我是f梅布利 - 稍等
No, Mabry. Hold on.
- 不行 - 槭颤N
No. Why not?
你不能u掉苋鹈.吉安比
Because you can't trade Jeremy Giambi.
就他了 艾德
He'll be fine, Ed.
槭颤N我X得你在孜冶阋
Why do I get the feeling you're picking my pocket?
我]有 你才孜冶阋 光吉安比@名字都值更多
I'm not. You're picking mine. Giambi's name alone is worth more.
- 他有什N} - 他]}
What's wrong with him? Nothing.
所以@算是f好了 _始做文件了?
Can we say it's done in theory and start drawing up the paperwork?
- 好吧 不^你得… - 好O了
Okay, but you're gonna haVe... Great.
他想f
He was gonna say something else.
得到想要的回答就祀
When you get the answer you're looking for, hang up.
- K珊 - 在
Suzanne. Yes?
- 接大l.|布_夫斯基（底特律老虎） - 好
David Dombrowski. Okay.
- 佩{也得走 - 我X得你不能@N做
And Pena's going too. I don't think you should do that.
我真的X得你不能@
I really don't think you should do that.
我要哈特伯格今晚就上
I want Hatteberg in the lineup tonight.
比利 我想你等一等
You need to take a minute.
我真的X得你要想清楚在做什N
I think you seriously need to think about what you're doing.
- 因槟愫懿凰 - 好吧
Because you're upset. Okay.
我有什N]想到的
What am I missing?
@些Q定很y向人交待
These are hard moves to explain to people.
有} 皮特
Why is that a problem, Pete?
e意庥檬 比利
Don't make an emotional decision, Billy.
大l.|布_夫斯基在3
David Dombrowski's on 3.
著 我要做就做Q了
Look, we're gonna shake things up.
大l 佩{要公_出售了 我第一通知你
Dave. Pena's going on the block. You're my first call.
因樗本其他人@得很蠢
Because he's making the rest of the team look bad.
他得今年的新人哦
He's gonna be a Rookie of the Year.
- f不定可以入x全明星容 - 他M全明星 大l
Probably an All-Star. He's an All-Star, Dave.
不 我要後援投手加F金
No. I want a reliever and cash.
好吧 o你5分 大l ^r不候
Okay. You got five minutes, Dave. I'm not waiting.
比利 佩{是全明星的料啊
Billy, Pena is an All-Star, okay?
如果你u掉他 而哈特伯格 @招又]成功 你知道@…
And if you dump him and this Hatteberg thing doesn't work out, you know this is...
@NQ定足以你G掉工作
This is the kind of decision that gets you fired.
真的
It is.
你f的
Yes, you're right.
我可能G掉工作
I may lose my job.
而我44q的人 只有高中文{
In which case I'm a 44-year-old guy with a high school diploma
我想送我女鹤x大W
and a daughter I'd like to be able to send to college.
你25q 有耶Wv
You're 25 years old, with a degree from Yale
有很棒的工作
and a pretty impressive apprenticeship.
我K]有核心}
I don't think we're asking the right question.
我想我的是
I think the question we should be asking is,
你相信我的x
do you believe in this thing or not?
我信
I do.
你X得我需要 向e人解的就e了
It's a problem you think we need to explain ourselves.
不解 oφl
Don't. To anyone.
明白
Okay.
我要猿值降琢 oY局好
Now, I'm gonna see this thing through, for better or worse.
你只要告V我 你分析一臼怯 哈特伯格更有偎 是佩{
Just tell me, do you project we'll win more with Hatteberg or Pena at first?
Y果很接近…
It's close...
不^理上哈特伯格更好
but theoretically, Hatteberg.
那我U什N
What are we talking about, then?
|布_夫斯基又打砹 在3
Dombrowski's on again, on 3.
喂
Yeah?
好 可以
Okay, that'll work.
很好 有一件事
Great. I need one more thing.
汽水  我不想自己的球T再 花XI汽水
Soda. Yeah, I don't want my guys paying for soda.
我要你o我的汽水Ca三年
I want you to stock my machine for three years.
我是J真的
I'm serious.
好O了 f定了
Great. It's a deal.
去告V佩{ 他打包走人
Go tell Pena he's gotta pack.
- 你要我去告V佩{ - @是工作的一部分
You want me to tell Pena? Part of the job.
吉安比呢 也要我去f
What about Giambi? You want me to tell him too?
我
I'll tell him.
- 打_下 卡洛斯 - 什N事
Excuse me, Carlos? Yeah?
- 我能和你删 - 好的
Can I speak with you a minute? Yeah.
卡洛斯 你被D到底特律老虎了
Carlos, you've been traded to the Tigers.
@是.帕的
This is Jay Palmer's number.
他是球的差旅管理秘
He's the traveling secretary for the team.
他正等你的 他理其他一切事宜
He's expecting your call. He'll take care of everything.
- 就@恿? -
Is that it? Yes.
好吧
Okay.
好了
艾特 你F在有空
Art, you got a minute?
嗯 坐吧
Yeah. Take a seat.
今晚你不能首l佩{上一玖 你要用哈特伯格
You can't start Pena at first tonight. You'll have to start Hatteberg.
我不想再扯@} 比利
I don't wanna go 15 rounds, Billy.
M容的是我 U少f
The lineup card is mine, and that's all.
然 M容的是你
That lineup card is definitely yours.
我只是f一静荒苡门寮{了
I'm just saying you can't start Pena at first.
哦
Well...
我就要他去一
I am starting him at first.
我想不行了 他F在榈滋芈尚Яα
I don't think so. He plays for Detroit now.
你Q走了佩{？
You traded Pena?
]e
Yeah.
有曼{奇Z 希吉斯 塔姆被解聘了
And Menechino, Hiljus, Tam are all being sent down.
- 你了 - 是哦 我是子
You are outside your mind. Yeah. Cuckoo.
- 你想我? -  苋鹈 坐吧
You wanted to see me? Yeah, Jeremy, grab a seat.
苋鹈 我把你Q到M城人了
Jeremy, you've been traded to the Phillies.
@是艾德.f德的 他是球理 是好人
This is Ed Wade's number. He's a good guy, the GM.
你o他打吧
He's expecting your call.
布德湍阌wC
Buddy will help you with the plane flight.
你是好球T 苋鹈
You're a good ballplayer, Jeremy,
祝你好\
and we wish you the best.
苋鹈滓沧吡
Jeremy's gone too.
你要Я诉@球
You're killing this team.
艾特 我可以一直@N做下去
Art, I can do this all day long.
嘿
Hey.
你Υ撕oh?
You agree with this?
z毫]有
Hundred percent.
想要P上T
You want this door closed?
- 斯科特.H - 是的 先生?
Scotty H. Sir?
- 去接L地球吧 - 好的
Go field some grounders. Yes, sir.
大家好了
Everybody, listen up.
也S你看起聿幌窆谲
You may not look like a winning team...
但你就是
but you are one.
所以...
So...
今晚打出冠幼
play like one tonight.
要命了
Oh, shit.
舻侥阆g的球r 你的打袈适.625 相@人啊
When you're getting your pitch, you're hitting.625, massive.
你能把球打爆
You're crushing the ball.
但你y]...不挑你擅L冉钦中球r
But when you swing at things... Your pitch is middle-in.
而是]棒舻氖堑忘c外角球 你的打袈手挥.158
When you're swinging low and away, you're batting.158.
每打刀枷21c的一牌
Every at bat's like a hand of blackjack.
每l完一牌 局荻伎赡芊P
Every card that's dealt, your odds change.
所以一旦第一好球]糁 你的羟蚵示拖陆75c
So every first-pitch strike, your batting average goes down about 75 points.
75c啊
Seventy-five points.
Ψ酵妒在第五局前投出100球
He should throw 100 pitches before the fifth.
你得把首l投手o累趴下 他在牛棚Y起不
You wanna knock that starter out.
我要你在系列收Pr氖 甚至11投手那拿足打
I want you taking at bats off the 10th and 11 th pitcher by the end.
@Y的y分析@示了
This is your basic breakdown of the pitches,
你的所有理想羟螯c 以及原因
where you should be hitting them, why.
- 所以你是要我更多得被保送 - 得好 是的
So you want us to walk more? Good question. Yes.
Z斯蒂斯先生
Mr. Justice.
- 我有些想法 - 是
Had a few thoughts. Yeah?
- 是的 - 想教我什N
Yeah. Gonna teach me some things?
什N
Excuse me?
]^理 那痈球Tv
Never seen a GM talk to players like that.
你也]^^球T的理吧
You never seen a GM who was a player.
哈
Huh.
- 有什N} 大l - 不 ]什N
We got a problem, David? No, it's okay.
我知道你的套路
I know your routine.
@是碥的 榱诉_到效果
It's patter. It's for effect.
但@一套λ好用 ξ]用
But it's for them, all right? That shit ain't for me.
那你很特殊咯
Oh, you're special?
你每年o我700f美元 所以 是的
You're paying me 7 million bucks a year, man, so, yeah,
也S我是有c特e
maybe I am, a little bit.
不 夥 我]o你700f
No, man, I ain't paying you 7.
洋基了你一半薪水
Yankees are paying half your salary.
@就是~s洋基δ愕B度
That's what the New York Yankees think of you.
他o你350f美元 你碜鏊的κ
They're paying you $3.5 million to play against them.
你到底想f什N 比利
Where you going with this, Billy?
大l 你37q了
David, you're 37.
不如我坦白c ff彼此想要什N
How about you and I be honest about what each of us want out of this?
我要榨干你最後一滴棒球能力
I wanna milk the last ounce of baseball you got in you.
而你想留在錾
And you wanna stay in the show.
我合作吧
Let's do that.
我不是槟阍的x煌o你X
I'm not paying you for the player you used to be.
而就是看上F在的你
I'm paying you for the player you are right now.
你很明 你明白我想做什N
You're smart. You get what we're trying to do here.
o年p人做榜影
Make an example for the younger guys.
Iд
Be a leader.
你能做到
Can you do that?
好吧 我知道了
All right. I got you.
我之g]}了吧
We're cool?
]}
We're cool.
斯科特.H
Scotty H.
- 你好 D.J. - 烨C器哈
Yo, what's up, D. J? Picking machine.
喜g一 夥
How you liking first base, man?
有M展吧 ^m烨虬
It's coming along. Picking it up.
你知道 D很困y 不^我感X越碓胶昧
You know, tough transition, but I'm starting to feel better with it.
- 是 - 嗯
Yeah? Yeah.
你最怕什N
What's your biggest fear?
任何朝我w淼陌羟
A baseball being hit in my general direction.
很好笑 f真的 是什N
That's funny. Seriously, what is it?
真的 就是@
No, seriously, that is.
嘿 那祝你好\啊
Well, hey, good luck with that.
要多社交啊
Be social out there.
- 社交 - 社交 就像GAP的迎eT
Social. Social. Like a greeter at the Gap.
有人跑到你的地P 就和他聊聊
Guy steps into your office, chat him up.
你x^ 上^W
You're well-read. You went to school.
-  - _心c 放
Yeah. Have some fun. Relax.
每人都想M攻 不要老想M攻
Everyone wants to attack. Quit trying to attack.
比跟著你的奏走 @|西不限rg的
Let the game come to you, man. There's no clock on this thing.
@是消耗
This is a war of attrition.
我可以多放^c球 甚至放^好球 被保送上镜茁室苍酱
If I take more, I could even take a few strikes, but I'll get walked more.
只要上 我就A 上不了 我就
You get on base, we win. You don't, we lose.
我球 查威 我
And I hate losing, Chavvie. I hate it.
比起想A 我更
I hate losing more than I even wanna win.
@是有^e的
And there's a difference.
- 不要|舳檀 - 短打就意味著一人出局
No bunts. Bunts is an out.
- 就算三臼轴嵬艘膊恍 - 不管怎右膊灰短打
Even if the third baseman is back? No bunting whatsoever.
如果Ψ奚短打 直接烨蛉咏o一
If someone bunts on us, throw it to first.
e逞英雄了想p
Don't be a hero and go to second.
等著橙朔稿e`
Let them make the mistakes.
你橙朔稿er ^Σ灰打_他
When your enemy's making mistakes, don't interrupt them.
他是在o你C 你踢他出局
They're giving you an out. Just giving it to you.
抓住C 道x就好
Take it. Say thank you.
有一件事 不要I
Another thing. No more stealing.
但我就擅LI 你雇我砭褪亲我I
That's what I do, what you pay me to do.
我雇你榱苏旧弦 不是榱吮唤⒃诙
I pay you to get on first, not get thrown out at second.
@是^程 ^程 知道
This is a process. It's a process, it's a process. Okay?
苌（洋基的吉安比）接住球 扔o二 一出局 \蛹谊得一分
Jason takes it, goes to second for the only out, and the A 's get a run.
苓~恩.戴又一支全敬 @是他霰荣中的第二支了
Jermaine Dye homers again, his second in two games.
\蛹谊在猿 @Y是目前的e分 （2002年6月6日）
And the A 's are still hanging in. We'll get you scores here.
\蛹谊和天使的俨畋焕近了 只差2鼍湍苡CZ外卡
The A 's pull within two of the Angels for the wild-card chase.
tmF在已B5
The Reds haVe now dropped fiVe in a row
在@鱿盗匈一_始就被W克m 以5比3I先
as Oakland beats them in the beginning of this series 5 to 3.
塔哈_被保送了
Tejada walks.
四那
Ball four.
四那 哈特伯格被保送上
Ball four and Hatteberg walks.
W克ml生什N了 \蛹谊已BmA了7
What is happening in Oakland? The A 's haVe won seven in a row.
真是令人d^ @是萑绯卑
A lot of excitement. What a winning streak.
不是艾特.哈住了心
But how about the calming influence of Art Howe?
如果不是指我或者皮特 那你指的消息碓淳屯耆不知所^
When you say "your source," if it's not me or Peter, they don't know.
他ьI著一不同こ５年伍
He's managing an unorthodox team.
-  - @容K不出色
Right. It's not a perfect roster.
但F在艾特.哈才是 @支伍倮的原因
But right now, Art Howe is the reason this team is winning.
- 他值得@拥陌 - 好 xx 再
He deserves the credit. Great, thanks. Bye.
你了
Did you hear that?
我到"BmA了7" 你拿到克利夫m的攻防名瘟
I heard "seven in a row." You get the Cleveland matchups?
就在@Y
Yeah, right here.
- 布斯 - 比利
Voos. Billy.
- @Y的味道更y了 - 我@就理
That smell is getting worse. I'm on it.
- 今晚怎N打算 - 各半怎N
What are we doing? Splitting it in half?
- 左右蛇都要 - 好的
Both sides of the plate. Got it.
- 赫迪 得Q球路 - 好的 先生
Huddy. Mix it up. Yes, sir.
- 相信你的旋D球 - 好的
Trust your slider, yeah? Yes, sir.
你e再他分心了
You guys quit distracting him.
你昨晚不急著打那些球啊
You couldn't hit that shit last night with a paddle.
多等浊蚵
You gotta see more pitches.
- 好的 比利 - 要有耐心
All right, Billy. Patience.
- 嘿 大l - 嘿 比利
Hey, David. Hey, Billy.
- 打得好 - xx
Great at bats. Thank you.
很有|量
Really quality. Thank you.
右外野安打 塔哈_得分
Base hit to right field. Tejada scores.
查f斯也跑回本玖 球w^了w
ChaVez coming in. The ball gets past Guiel.
\蛹谊以5比0落後 反超6比5I先
The A 's, from 5-nothing down, now lead 6 to 5.
投手生涯o
F在W克m\蛹谊直是\野R
The Oakland A 's are completely out of hand at the moment.
美盟後援投手
他@得174 是美本月最好的成
They are an AL-best 17 and 4 this month.
他在波士D和~s也接B@
They also took back-to-back series at Boston and at new York.
得六月r他苋鹈.吉安比 uoM城人
Remember when they traded Jeremy Giambi in June
所有人都J樗放了
and everyone thought they'd just giVen up?
其正相反
Actually, not so much.
2002 球T交易截止日
K珊 接史派_
Suzanne, get Shapiro on the phone.
- 你想要林康? -  他的季Y束了 他]信心了
You thinking Rincon? His season's done. He's lost faith.
- 我想R克他 - 猜得妙啊
I think he's gonna dump him. Hard-core.
史派_在2
Shapiro on 2.
R克 是我比利 我_T山吧
Mark, Billy. Let's be honest.
靠一秀的後援投手是不可能 湍阙A得季後的
A premier setup man isn't gonna get you closer to the play-offs.
你是指林康
Are you referring to Rincon?
夥 你可不起@奢侈品
He's a luxury you can't afford, man.
你能 他合同上要付50f
And you can? There's half a million on his contract.
而且要I他的人不止一啊
And we'Ve got at least one other suitor.
"不止一"就是只有一吧
By "at least one," you mean one.
- 是l - 我不想f
Who is it? I'd rather not say.
f金山巨人
San Francisco. San Francisco.
^涸俅蚪o你
I'll call you back.
你X得我用格{迪能Ql
What do you think we can get for Magnante?
什N也Q不了
Nothing.
- f{夫_的合同上剩多少 - 27.5f
What's left on Venafro's contract? Two seventy-five.
K珊 臀医尤鲑e恩
Suzanne, get me Sabean on the line.
巨人d趣D到f{夫_身上 要I林康的就只剩一
Get the Giants interested in Venafro, Mark's only got one buyer for Rincon.
- 就是我 - 他在3
Us. On 3.
_比 我是比利 你X得f{夫_怎
Saby-Sabster, it's Billy. What do you think of Venafro?
我半u半送o你
I can let you have him for almost nothing.
- 你安的什N心呢 - 因槲沂好人
Why would you do that? Because I'm amazing.
我就要cX和一附加l件
I want a couple bucks and a sweetener.
你就o我…
Throw in, say...
- 安德森 - 安德森
Anderson. Anderson.
- 我喜g安德森 - 你才不 ]人喜g安德森
I like Anderson. No, you don't. Nobody likes him.
我都不知道我致镞@N做 但就@影
I don't know why I'm doing this. But let's do it.
- f{夫_Q~克森 - 安德森 - 我是f安德森 我都不知道他叫什N
Venafro for Michaelson. Anderson. I don't know his name.
- 我考]下 - 好好考] o我
I'll think about it. Think about it and call me back.
接史派_
Get Shapiro on.
史派_在2
Shapiro's on 2.
- R克 - 你I不起他 比利
Mark. You can't afford him, Billy.
你_定
You sure about that?
怎N我X得林康]什N市隽
I get the impression the market for Rincon is softening.
- 啊? - 我可能e了
Huh? I could be wrong,
如果我是你
but I'd call whoever's interested
我打o之前有d趣的人 得回我哦
and see if they're still interested. Call me back.
- 大都f{夫_有d趣 - 你把他Io巨人啊
What about the Mets for Venafro? You offered him to the Giants.
K珊 接史蒂夫.w利浦
Suzanne, Steve Phillips.
巨人有邦 肯特 南 史Z 才不要f{夫_
Between Bonds, Kent, Nen, Snow, San Francisco's never gonna do it.
- 完全同意 - 我只是要他放林康
Totally agree. We just need them to cool on Rincon.
- w利浦在2 - 史蒂夫 是我比利
Phillips on 2. Steve-o, it's Billy.
我f你想要左手後援投手 我可以o你f{夫_
I hear you're looking for a reliever. I can give you Venafro.
- 瘟水 - 你有啥企D
I can make it quick and easy. What's the angle?
- ]企D啊 - 那你想拐跑l
No angle. Who am I getting fleeced for?
- 等等 - 本{特怎N
Hang on a sec. Uh, Bennett, maybe?
- 年g - 26
How old? Twenty-six.
26q 在2A（培B後涞男÷盟） 不行
Twenty-six, Double-A? Forget it.
肯 不行
Duncan, no.
不行 弗布什 不行
No. Furbush, no.
艾肯特怎N 就
Eckerton? Eckerton? Eckerton.
Eckerton.
- 我喜g艾肯特 - 你根本都不知道他是l
I like Eckerton. You don't even know who Eckerton is.
- f{夫_受了 - ]有 他很好
Is Venafro hurt? No, he's fine, he's fine.
只是我炔坑悬c}
It's just an issue for us.
- 之前纱 他投球都被麸w了 - 不是他的}
Last couple times, he got hammered. Not his fault.
- 是我的} 策略e` - 是史蒂夫
That was us. We misused him. It's Steve.
- 就快好了 - 史蒂夫.莎特（老）
I'm almost done. Steve Schott.
- 稍等 他在打 - 著史蒂夫 我直接跟你f吧
Look, Steve-o, let me be straight with you.
是@拥 我要了林康 已好了
Here's the deal. I'm getting Rincon. It's a done deal.
- 但我f巨人… - 不 巨人想用~克森Qf{夫_
I heard the Giants... Giants want Venafro for Michaelson.
- 是安德森 - 我Qo你
Anderson. I'd rather deal with you.
你可以o我艾肯特和22.5fF金
You can give me Eckerton and $225,000 in cash,
巨人什N都]有
and the Giants can't.
- 我考]一下 - 考]吧
I'll think about it. Think about it.
不^l先回我 f{夫_就wl
But whoever calls me back first gets Venafro.
莎特（老）炝
Schott hung up.
我一定要成功
Oh, I want this one.
槭颤N]人打戆
Why isn't anybody calling?
史派_在2
Shapiro's on 2.
喂
Yeah?
好 我跟老 然後回你 xx
Okay, let me talk to my owner. I'll call you back.
- 接史蒂夫的 - 莎特（老）是w利浦（大都）
Get Steve on the phone. Schott or Phillips?
我嵋打ow利浦 是他打o我
Why would we call Phillips? Phillips has gotta call us.
告V他 我在打
Tell him I'm on the other line.
嗨 莎特先生 我是皮特.布m德 很抱歉要你等候
Hi, Mr. Schott, it's Peter Brand. I apologize for putting you on hold.
- 比利叫我回你 他在打 - f我要22.5fI林康
Billy asked me to call you back. Tell him we want 225,000 for Rincon.
比利f他要22.5fIY卡多.林康
Billy says he needs $225,000 for Ricardo Rincon.
你
Please.
是 是我加的"你"二字
Yes, I added the "please" at the end.
好吧 我...稍等一下
Okay. Let me... Hold on one second, please.
告V他 我斫oX
Tell him I'll pay for him.
但如果明年我把他u了p倍rX 那得w我
But when I sell him back for twice the amount next year, I keep the money.
好 比利f他自己付XI林康
Okay, so Billy says he'll pay for Rincon himself.
但明年如果u了高r 利都w他了
But when he sells him for more money next year, he's keeping the profit.
非常感x 我再打o你 xx
Thank you very much. We'll call you back. Thank you.
戆 再
Come on. Come on.
K珊 打o史派_ 算了 他打砹
Suzanne, call Shapiro ba... Never mind, I got him right here.
R克 是我
Mark. Yeah.
著 我可不要林康今晚跟我打μ
Listen, I don't want Rincon pitching against me tonight.
告V他Q服 送他^ X浜昧
Tell him to change clothes and send him over. I got you the money.
Yup.
太好了
Great.
我不想破夥 但我有了林康...
I don't wanna dampen the mood at all, but since we picked up Rincon...
就要踢某人出局了
We gotta send someone down.
- 格 - 嗨 比利
Mags. Hey, Billy.
我知道最近我有c吃力
I know I've been struggling lately.
但下半季一定有改善的 Y奇和我想到…
But second half of the season, definitely turn it around. Ricky and l...
格 不要再整b了
Mike, I need you to stop getting dressed.
我被u了?
Traded?
很抱歉Ыo你南息
I'm sorry for the crap news.
我知道@很痛苦
I know it hurts.
格 球Y不能有26人
Mike, I can't have 26 guys in the clubhouse.
我知道 我知道
I get it. I get it.
好的 xx
Okay. Thanks.
嘿 Y卡多
Hey, Ricardo.
- 你好 先生 - 你好
@一定你吃了一@吧
This must be a bit of a shock, I guess.
梅布利糁幸磺 球wM中右外野
Mabry hits one deep to right-center field.
跑者已跑回本 菲克接不到了
Racing back, Fick can't get it.
球到得分牌板上 一跑回本 跑回本
It bounces to the wall. One run is in. Two runs are in.
梅布利一球之g 就o\蛹谊眍I先
Mabry, on one pitch, has shot the A 's in front.
三振 \蛹谊B12隽 （B伲
Strike three called. TwelVe straight wins for the Athletics.
天呢 太不可思h了
Man aliVe, was it hairy.
W克m出了怪事了
Something strange is now happening in Oakland.
- F在分o可置疑了 - B12
You cannot argue that point.  TwelVe straight.
他美棒球盟成了笑
They're making a joke out of the American League.
- 他今天在底特律 - 他鹘o一
They were in Detroit today...  He throws to first.
@就是14B俚g呼
And that's the sound of 14 straight Victories.
14 @是今年的最高
Fourteen, the longest run this year.
\蛹谊已攀升到美西^第一名 倮一l不可收拾
It has slingshot the A 's into first in the AL West. A nice streak.
@支球曾一度被o情抨
This team was written off.
如何解他取得的@人倮
How do you explain, otherwise, the Victories they'Ve come up with?
W克m\蛹谊A得了16鲞B
The Oakland A 's are gonna win 16 consecutiVe games.
@是25年戆羟蚪缱铋L的B儆 ^
This is the longest win streak in baseball, folks, in 25 years.
\蛹谊已B16隽
The A 's haVe won 16 in a row.
我要20B 20B
We're going to 20! We're going to 20!
要BmA到F在 伍一定很秀
To haVe a winning streak of this duration, you haVe to be good,
但@Y面也有偶然性
but there's an element of randomness to it.
1927年的洋基 有路德 w瑞格 有⑹执蚓（o年洋基大容的昵Q）
The 1927 Yankees, Ruth, Gehrig,
至今仍有人J槭亲秀的容
Murderers' Row, some people still say the best team ever.
他年最L的倮是多少 9B
Longest winning streak for them that year? Nine.
你想用一系列的^c矸治鲞@事
You guys try to analyze it from a numbers standpoint.
我告V你 F在l生的事 o法解
I'm telling you, there is no explanation for what's occurring right now.
你是用了什N巫g
Do you haVe superstitions going on?
你做了什N才能保持B俚?
Do you do things so you keep the streak aliVe?
破o的20B倏雌 K非不可能
The all-time record of 20 does not seem impossible anymore.
今天\蛹谊上了~sr代sI
The A 's were on page one of the New York Times.
他是整家w育界的髌
They are the story in sports in this entire country.
珊 看@
Two-two pitch, here it is.
]棒落空 三振出局 第17
Swing and a miss! Struck him out! Number 17!
用71年了
It's taken 71 years.
W克m\蛹谊平了M城人的o
The Oakland A 's haVe tied the Philadelphia A 's.
空前^後的17B儆
The all-time franchise record 17 straight
自1953年以 棒球史上最L的B儆
and baseball's longest winning streak since 1953.
差 \蛹谊就能平了美了
The A 's are two wins away from tying the American League record.
w出去了 w出去了 塔哈_全敬 你能相信
It's gone! It's gone! Tejada wins it! Do you believe it?
B18
Eighteen wins in a row!
你可以重}看那18次比100遍
You could replay these 18 games a hundred times oVer.
]人能再次B18
And nobody wins 18 straight again.
@覆了我Π羟蛩有的^念
It defies everything we know about baseball.
^去4天Y 大w育鲅Yl生了
The most amazing thing you could imagine
你能想像到最神奇的事
happened oVer the last four days at the coliseum.
塔哈_ 直w中野 \蛹谊B19隽
Tejada, up the middle. The A 's haVe won 19 in a row!
1906年的白m
The 1906 White Sox,
1947年的洋基 他有伴了
the 1947 new York Yankees haVe company.
B19
Nineteen in a row.
\蛹谊c倮有s
The A 's haVe a date with destiny.
他直奔美盟的而去
They're going for the all-time American League record,
B20
20 games in a row.
我要20B 我要把刷新到20B
We're going to 20! We're gonna take the AL record to 20, baby!
2002年 9月4日
e告V我分 皮特
Don't tell me the score, Pete.
不 比利 是我
No, Billy, it's me.
- 莎 - 是的
Sharon? Yeah.
- 你有rg - 有 怎N了
You haVe a second? Yeah, what's up?
我倒]想到你接起
Well, I didn't actually expect you to pick up.
本硐肓口信的
I was gonna leaVe a message.
P西和我 我在家正在看比
Um, casey and I, we're here and watching the game at home.
我想告V你
And I just wanted to say...
你做得很棒 比利
you did good, Billy.
我槟泸傲
We're really proud of you.
xx 莎
I appreciate it, Sharon.
- xx - 祝你好\
Thank you. Good luck.
嗯
Okay.
P西想跟你f 等等
Oh, casey wants to talk to you. Hang on.
你正在去\龅穆飞
Are you on your way to the stadium?
不 我正要去S利 去看我的小盟 （附凫洞舐盟伍送後^T）
No, I'm on my way to Visalia to see our minor-league team.
- 快掉^啊 爸爸 - ]T
Turn around, please, Dad. No way, Jose.
- 掉^吧 拜 老爸 - 不 不行
Turn around. Come on, Dad. Nope. Not gonna happen.
你不去厄\啦
You're not gonna jinx it.
回^再聊 甜心 我勰
I'll talk to you later, sweetheart. I love you.
的
Shit.
第四局一人出局 如果你D到@l道
One out here in the fourth, and if you're just joining us,
你e^了很多精彩啊
you missed a lot.
到保_.依e尼羟 一好球
And the pitch to Raul Ibanez. Strike one.
我的述很
I think my recap will be simple.
\蛹谊第一局得了6分 第二局1分 第三局4分
The A 's scored six in the first, one in the second, four in the third.
你f得@虞p巧 到的人吃@啦 哈哈哈
And people would be shocked if you just did that. Heh-heh-heh.
11比0 \蛹谊I先
Eleven to nothing, the A 's do lead.
- 的 - 界外 好球…
Shit. Foul off the foot of Ibanez...
n啊 W克m
Let's go, Oakland!
F在上羟 2 捕手布m特.梅恩
Now batting, number 2, catcher, Brent Mayne.
- W克m - 上啊 W克m
Oakland! Here we go, Oakland!
Two.
安全上
Safe.
F在上羟
Now batting,
18 左外野手保_.依e尼
number 18, left fielder Raul Ibanez.
安全回
Safe.
F在\蛹谊以11比3I先
And the A 's now lead by a score of 11 to 3.
n下是不e 但不oκC
A nice cushion, but you don't wanna giVe teams life
不能他有翻P的C 即使I先…
and let them wedge their way back in, even when you're...
]人出局 M
Nobody out, the bases loaded.
艾特.哈正走向投手丘 要作投球{整
And Art Howe on the way to the mound to make a pitching change.
@霰荣的局面仍然可能
And this game is still in a state
超出\蛹谊的掌控
where it could get out of control for the Athletics.
某r刻 有人告V我 不能再玩小孩子的[
We're all told at some point we can no longer play the children's game.
只是不知道是何r
We just don't know when that's gonna be.
可能是在18q 可能是在40q 但我有那r刻
Some of us are told at 18, some of us are told at 40, but we're all told.
F在是克.斯S尼打 一救居腥
Mike Sweeney with runners at first and third.
F在比分11比7 \蛹谊I先
It's an 11-to-7 game, the A 's in front.
塔姆等著投手手
Tam peering in for the sign.
扇顺鼍 一三居腥
Two out. Runners at first and third.
珊萌模ㄇ狄M 下一球要N 三人出局此局Y束 要NO可能得分）
And the 3-2 deliVery.
（@球是全敬 @右蝗居腥 意味著一下子得三分）
@太怪了比利
It's weird, Billy.
你想放打棒球 去球探？
You wanna giVe up baseball to become a scout?
我不是棒球球手
I'm not a baseball player.
你_定@是你想要的
Are you sure this is what you want?
人群在咆哮 肯什浜昧 珊靡
The crowd is roaring. Koch is ready. One-two pitch.
阿里西打出去了 弧w到左外野 一支安打
Alicea puts it in play, a looper to left field for a base hit.
跑^三 直n本 平分了
Around third, tearing for the plate, here comes the tying run.
滑境晒 p方11分平
Sliding safe. And the ball game is tied at 11-all.
上帝啊
Holy Toledo.
\蛹谊浪M了11比0的I先
The A 's haVe blown an 11-to-nothing lead.
自幕始谊在第四局得到5分後
This is the specter of a development that has been lurking now
人心^的恐慌_始蔓延了
ever since the fiVe-run fourth inning by the Royals.
\蛹谊c倮的s出F停了
And the A 's date with destiny is on hold right now.
哈特伯格 哈特
Hatteberg. Hattie.
拿上球棒 你代布m{斯羟
Grab a bat. You're hitting for Byrnesy.
快c 悠 去嵘
Come on, let's go. Get yourself loose.
埃Y克.布m{斯代打
Hitting for Eric Byrnes,
10 斯科特.哈特伯格
number 10, Scott Hatteberg.
按\蛹谊T常的L格 派了能上镜娜松
In your typical A 's fashion. They want a base runner here.
斯科特.哈特伯格擅L得四那虮Ｋ
Scott Hatteberg is so adept at drawing walks.
教是想哈特伯格上
He's looking for Hatteberg to get on base,
再Q代跑
maybe bring in a pinch runner.
上啊 W克m
Let's go, Oakland!
球w出去了（全敬)
That one is gone!
@是W克m\蛹谊 第20鲞Bm倮
And it's 20 consecutiVe Victories for the Oakland Athletics
在@不可思h的夜晚
on an unbelieVable night
他失去了11比0的葜後
when they lost an 11-to-nothing lead
最後大@全
and now they win it.
人群重新陷入狂
The crowd comes back to insane life.
@是不解之迷啊
How do you explain it?
了 完全是了
Crazy. Just plain crazy.
哈特伯格在本旧媳淮蠹野
Hatteberg is mobbed at home plate.
在美棒球盟103年的v史上
In 103 years of American League baseball,
\蛹谊的倮前o古人
the Athletics haVe accomplished what no one has before.
他BmA得了20倮
They haVe won 20 consecutiVe games.
你]法不凵习羟
It's hard not to be romantic about baseball.
@N盛事 是球迷的狂g
This kind of thing, it's fun for the fans.
票房大u 峁肥垠
It sells tickets and hot dogs.
但毫o意x
Doesn't mean anything.
比利 我B20霭
Billy, we just won 20 games in a row.
所以呢
And what's the point?
我造了
We just got the record.
夥 我做@行已…
Man, I've been doing this for...
著 夥
Listen, man.
我在@一行的rg很L了
I've been in this game a long time.
我不是榱思o淼 告V你
I'm not in it for a record, I'll tell you that.
我不是榱斯谲指h
I'm not in it for a ring.
@Nr候 有人付出代r
That's when people get hurt.
如果最後一龉谲我了
If we don't win the last game of the Series,
他照硬在意我
they'll dismiss us.
- 比利... - 我t解@些人
Billy... I know these guys.
我知道他的想法 他抹平我的成就
I know the way they think, and they will erase us.
我做的一切
And everything we've done here,
λ都毫o意x
none of it'll matter.
其他任何球A了冠都是件好事
Any other team wins the World Series, good for them.
他_香 @得冠戒
They're drinking champagne, they get a ring.
但如果我A了
But if we win,
用@拥念A算 @拥那蜿
on our budget, with this team...
我就改了一切[蛞t
we'll have changed the game.
@才是我要的
And that's what I want.
我要@事留下意x
I want it to mean something.
W克m\蛹谊 е西^冠^M入季後
The A 's going to the play-offs with the West DiVision title.
他未大肆c祝 @情有可原
ForgiVe the A 's if they're not celebrating.
他之前也走到^@Y
They haVe been here before,
就在去年 \蛹谊在美季候 分^BA^洋基
when Oakland went up two games to none on the Yanks in the ALDS,
之後s直三 |羽而w
and went nowhere after losing three straight.
今天A了p城 W克m⒃1992年後
With a win today oVer the Twins, Oakland moVes into the ALcS
第一次挺M美冠
for the first time since 1992.
但住一件事
But remember one thing.
整季的打袈士梢院芨 可是就一霰荣 一打而言
Percentages hold up oVer a season, but for one game, one at bat,
打袈]有任何意x
throw the percentages out the window.
明尼K_p子揭露了 W克m\蛹谊的真相
What the Minnesota Twins exposed is the fact that the Oakland A 's
他K究不是一支力酝Φ那蜿
were fundamentally not a sound baseball team.
那蜿理到智囊F都著一
They had a flawed concept that started with the general manager
e`的^念 就是他可以改棒球t
and the brain trust thinking they could reinVent baseball.
不能用空中情w的y概念
You can't approach baseball
碓棒球\
from a statistical, bean-counting point of View.
倮需要通^打的比才能@得
It's won on the field with fundamental play.
你得I 短打 奚
You haVe to steal, you haVe to bunt, you haVe to sacrifice.
你得T站上得分位 再送他回
You gotta get men in scoring position, and you gotta bring them in.
@不是用一堆yW的花招就能Q淼
And you don't do that with a bunch of statistical gimmicks.
]有人可以改[蛞t
Nobody reinVents this game.
是我
Yeah.
我o意小看W克m主 不^@才是真正的棒球
Due respect to the Coliseum, but this is a ballpark.
]e
Yes, it is.
一阂黄鸪晕顼吧
We're gonna have some lunch in a little bit.
我潼c咖啡
Why don't I have some coffee sent up?
Denise?
xx你 丹尼斯
Thank you, Denise.
- xx - ]PS
Thanks. You're welcome.
你知道 她生日到了 我送她生日Y物
You know, it's her birthday and I need to get her a present,
但通常她才是臀姨舳Y物的人
but she's usually the one that does that for me.
你有什N提h
So do you have any ideas?
巾
Scarf.
你是f羊毛的?
You mean like wool?
不 我是指女人用作品的那N
No, I meant what women wear with... You know, decorative.
啊 我到哪喝ベI@啊
Ah. And where would I get something like that?
我不想失Y 但我已Bm赡贻掉分^
No disrespect, I just lost in five for the second year in a row.
我只想送她只保g球
Get her a bowling ball for all I care.
f得也是
Right.
史蒂夫告V我他已提出了ms
Well, Steve told me he's offering you a new contract.
是的
Yes.
那你槭颤N要回我
So why did you return my call?
因檫@是tm
Because it's the Red Sox.
因槲蚁嘈趴W可以破解比斯的魔咒 (1920年tm比斯被u後{咒 tmo法再得全冠)
Because I believe science might offer an answer to the Curse of the Bambino.
- 因槲衣f你l蛄吮.詹姆斯 -
Because I hear you hired Bill James. Yup.
槭颤N要@N久才有人l蛩 我真想不通
You know, why someone took so long to hire that guy is beyond me.
棒球界不喜g他
Well, baseball hates him.
是的 棒球界可以他
Well, baseball can hate him, you know.
X的一大好就是可以I很多|西
One of the great things about money is that it buys a lot of things,
@N奢侈包括了 不用管棒球界喜g什N
one of which is the luxury to disregard what baseball likes,
棒球界不喜g什N 它怎N想 不怎N想
doesn't like, what baseball thinks, doesn't think.
起砗芩
Ah. Sounds nice.
Well...
我很感激你的黼
I was grateful for the call.
- 你很感激? -
You were grateful? Yeah.
你用4100f美元M建了Q球
For 41 million, you built a play-off team.
你失去了戴蒙 吉安比 伊斯林豪森 佩{
You lost Damon, Giambi, Isringhausen, Pena,
然後你A的比 比他在的r候更多
and you won more games without them than you did with them.
你A的比跟洋基一佣
You won the exact same number of games that the Yankees won,
但洋基每倮平均花M1400f美元
but the Yankees spent 1.4 million per win,
而你只付出了26f美元
and you paid 260,000.
我知道你Dy得滴血 但第一打破牢的人
I know you're taking it in the teeth, but the first guy through the wall,
是受挫折的
he always gets bloody.
是 @不H威{到整I模式
Always. This is threatening not just a way of doing business,
在他的心目中 @威{到整\永砟
but in their minds, it's threatening the game.
真的 @威{到他的生存方式 他的碗
Really, what it's threatening is their livelihood, their jobs.
威{到他做事的方式
It's threatening the way that they do things.
每次出F@N事
Every time that happens,
o是政府行 是商I行 o是什N
whether it's a government, a way of doing business, whatever,
手握掌控嗟娜
the people who are holding the reins,
可以一手遮天的人
they have their hands on the switch,
他l
they go batshit crazy.
你看 那些不拆散F有球
I mean, anybody who's not tearing their team down right now
不按你的模式重M球的人
and rebuilding it using your model,
他就是缃^的恐
they're dinosaurs.
今年10月 他坐在自家沙l上
They'll be sitting on their ass on the sofa in October
眼看著波士Dtm A得世界大冠
watching the Boston Red Sox win the World Series.
@是什N
What's this?
我要你我的球理 @是我_的r
I want you to be my general manager. That's my offer.
注意啊
Heads up.
你致锇
What was that?
- 抱歉 我也不知道 - 你搞什N啊
Sorry. I don't know. What the hell was that?
你i^
You knucklehead.
波士D之行如何
How was Boston?
印象深刻
Impressive.
亨利o了你很好的待遇吧
Did Henry make you a good offer, at least?
- oPo要 ]什N的 - 是怎 是怎
Doesn't matter. Doesn't matter. What was it? What was it?
- @oPo要 - 到底是什N
Doesn't matter. What was it?
你是w育史上 薪水最高的理啊
That makes you the highest-paid GM in the history of sports.
所以呢
So?
又怎
So what?
我曾做^一向X看的Q定
I made one decision in my life based on money.
我l^誓 ^不再犯
And I swore I would never do it again.
你@次不是榱隋X
You're not doing it for the money.
- 不是 - 不是
No? No.
你是榱诉@X的意x
You're doing it for what the money says.
它代表著每大X的球T 都知道的意x
And it says what it says to any player that makes big money.
就是他值得@rX
That they're worth it.
@都什N屁
What a dump.
我真的想在@Y取得倮
I really wanted to win here.
我真的想
I really did.
我X得你已大@全倭 比利
I think you won pretty big, Billy.
皮特 我了
Pete, we lost.
我了
We lost.
才滋於已 你得o自己一crg走出
It's only been a few days. Give yourself some time to get over it.
夥 我永h[不了@
Man, I don't get over these things.
永h
Ever.
跟我到像室 有|西o你看
Come with me to the video room. I wanna show you something.
不了 我F在]心情
No, man, I'm not up for film right now.
f真的
Come on. Seriously.
^ 比利 跟我
Come on, Billy. Come on.
S塞利的W克m小盟
The Visalia Oaks
以及我220斤的捕手苋鹈.布朗
and our 240-pound catcher, Jeremy Brown,
你知道的 他跑二臼且他命了
who, as you know, is scared to run to second base.
@是六周前的一霰荣
This was in a game six weeks ago.
@人投快球
This guy's gonna start with a fastball.
苋鹈滓把球打到中後方
Jeremy's gonna take him to deep center.
@是最有趣的地方了
Here's what's interesting,
因苋鹈状蛩阕 他]做^的事
because Jeremy's gonna do what he never does.
他要拼了
He's gonna go for it.
他@^一 然後全力n向二
He's gonna round first and he's gonna go for it.
浜昧
Okay?
@直就是苋鹈椎呢舫烧
This is all of Jeremy's nightmares coming to life.
- 他在笑他 - 苋鹈遵R上就要知道槭颤N了
Aw, they're laughing at him. And Jeremy's about to find out why.
苋鹈滓庾R到
Jeremy's about to realize
球w出了60英尺h
that the ball went 60 feet over the fence.
他打出了全敬 而自己都]lX
He hit a home run and didn't even realize it.
你怎N能不凵习羟 （猛c^）
How can you not be romantic about baseball?
- @是在[喻你 - 我知道是在f我
It's a metaphor. I know it's a metaphor.
好了
Okay.
皮特 你是好人
Pete, you're a good egg.
我打o你
I'll call you.
嘿 老爸 @是我f了u的歌
Hey, Dad, this is the song I told you I'd record.
不要oe人啊
Please don't show it to anyone else.
如果你改主意 留在加利福利 得告V我
Let me know if you change your mind and stay in california.
即使]有 你也是最好的爸爸
If not, you're a really great dad.
* 我有c左右呻y *
* I'm just a little bit caught in the middle *
* 生活是座迷m 矍槭iF *
* Life is a maze And loVe is a riddle *
* 我不知道去哪 我o法自完成 我努力了 *
* I don't know where to go can't do it alone, I'Ve tried *
* 我不知道槭颤N *
* And I don't know why *
* 我只是迷失在此刻的小女孩 *
* I'm just a little girl Lost in the moment *
* 管害怕 但我s不流露 *
* I'm so scared But I don't show it *
* 我]有k法 快被艨 *
* I can't figure it out It's bringing me down *
* 我知道 我得放手 *
* I know I'Ve got to let it go *
* 好好享受@鲂 *
* And just enjoy the show *
* 慢下 停下 *
* Slow it down, make it stop *
* 不然我的心K就要跳出砹 *
* Or else my heart Is going to pop *
* 因樘多 快要承受不了 *
* 'cause it's too much Yeah, it's a lot *
* @不是我 *
* To be something I'm not *
* 我是傻瓜 ]人 *
* I'm a fool, out of loVe *
* 可是我想要更多 *
* And I just can't get enough *
* 我有c左右呻y *
* I'm just a little bit caught in the middle *
* 生活是座迷m 矍槭iF *
* Life is a maze And loVe is a riddle *
* 我不知道去哪 我o法自完成 我努力了 *
* I don't know where to go can't do it alone, I'Ve tried *
* 我不知道槭颤N *
* And I don't know why *
比利拒^tm_出的1250f美金的年薪
* I'm just a little girl Lost in the moment *
他x窳粼W克m檫\蛹倚Я
* I'm so scared But I don't show it *
* I can't figure it out It's bringing me down *
赡赆 tmA得自1918年以淼 第一座世界大冠
* I know I'Ve got to let it go *
裼玫恼是W克m的棒球哲W
* And just enjoy the show *
* Dum-dee-dum Da-dum-dee-dum *
比利仍fDA得世界大冠
* Just enjoy the show *
* You're such a loser, Dad You're such a loser, Dad *
* 你是失≌ 爸爸 享受@鲂惆 *
* You're such a loser, Dad Just enjoy the show *
* You're such a loser, Dad You're such a loser, Dad *
* 你是失≌ 爸爸 *
* You're such a loser, Dad *
* 享受@鲂惆 *
* Just enjoy the show **
FRSrgS招聘群：37304379
FRM翻gM招聘]箱：frzhaopin2@gmail.com c最新美∮H密接| 享受海量FTP下d
LFRM字幕M作品
-==http://www.1000fr.net==-
g迎加入